[
  {
    "question": "What red object is the below the windows?",
    "answer": "Fire extinguisher",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "e845f82a-d55c-42f8-88e3-8e9fcaf5bd02",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food is on the counter?",
    "answer": "Cheerios",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b0b40220-5e47-40ea-9298-167b140c242c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the blinds?",
    "answer": "White",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "f829e253-ca9a-4456-b2d3-70e1a7a2eecd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the trashcan?",
    "answer": "In the corner",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "14774f3f-d14b-4e18-b5de-6e827a4d9e94",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the paper towels?",
    "answer": "Above the trashcan",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "a403b6f1-5e99-4644-aad6-772a0c9d8f90",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the countertop clean?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "016fb5d2-3c6f-4aa3-8493-7768aa3762a9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are all cabinet drawers closed?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "e6499416-f118-4c1b-aa99-a0b980b89e47",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I crack open the windows?",
    "answer": "Turn the window knob",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "48128095-6cec-4cf2-a282-bf380146ce0c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I eat?",
    "answer": "Cereal",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "d5ee5c7d-f02b-4a62-884d-92f83db9a541",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the kitchen in a home or public space?",
    "answer": "Public space",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "933a8957-9f4a-4836-bfb6-001fb82afdf8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What brand makes the cereal?",
    "answer": "General Mills",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "84104329-7c12-44d0-9582-f7767712af0a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the fire extinguisher?",
    "answer": "Under the windows",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "df48ef29-6497-4d5c-b673-0ccdeef26622",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Below the right window.",
      "To the right of the heater and to the left of the refridgerator.",
      "On the wall under the window",
      "Near the window"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the cereal?",
    "answer": "Behind the soap",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "7df7d40a-5a41-46f5-b738-767a5cfa14f2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/002-scannet-scene0709_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "To the right of the sink. ",
      "On the counter to the left of the microwave. ",
      "At the right of the sink",
      "On the kitchen counter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the blue object behind the tissue box and next to the phone on the table?",
    "answer": "Lysol cleaning wipes",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "30d7a3fe-abd8-4db0-91a1-28195f49c321",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the wire for the headphones?",
    "answer": "blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "1392c3bc-4899-4728-85b1-e4458282ed22",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the soda can?",
    "answer": "purple or red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "ce2f5613-88a1-4401-86dc-cbb968f56179",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there space under the table by the window?",
    "answer": "no, there are shoes, a machine and a trash bin",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "c9f3033f-3fc5-4859-a210-1ee90b212a14",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does the table with the monitor have space for a few more cup?",
    "answer": "yes there is space by the keyboard and mouse",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "5c047691-c116-45c7-a553-4493bbc1b949",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the drawers by the window open?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "b80f70ac-8df9-4015-ac47-7696271f4b12",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the desk with the monitor raised or lowered?",
    "answer": "Raised since it is higher than the desk next to it",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "69bf0e59-17d1-42b9-822b-a436fe661ef3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there anything I can pour my soda into?",
    "answer": "Yes theres a cup to the left of the desk.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "3e07db8f-2ef4-4239-9e27-e8c5d5d5ed36",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there anything to help me open a package?",
    "answer": "yes there are two scissors in the cup with the rainbow flag",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a14a11ee-ad00-4e7b-835d-687f23df5b80",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to take some notes, what can I use?",
    "answer": "There are post-its, paper, and notebooks on the two desks",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "f7186ea1-ebd6-450f-b27d-d9419e80ec2b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I would like to focus for some finite time, how can I time myself?",
    "answer": "Use the hourglass",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "8d62dfe4-eeb9-4d49-b92d-6aae2bf0c665",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my glasses case?",
    "answer": "On the table next to the fish tank, by the window",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "8d3b0032-f897-4bf3-9a5d-c03595760309",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the right side of the desk by the window",
      "next to the fish tank",
      "On the cluttered table, close to the standing desk",
      "On the table, next to the fish tank"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you seen my yellow highlighter?",
    "answer": "on the  desk to the right, right next to the monitor stand",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "7e8cd422-e00d-4a3b-814b-4245162bda80",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/003-scannet-scene0762_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "in front of the monitor",
      "next to the keyboard",
      "Yes, on the standing desk between the keyboard and the monitor",
      "Yes, on the desk in front of the monitor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fruit can you see on the dining table?",
    "answer": "banana",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "56f1da24-d4ad-4f6f-8630-b3d80e6e205e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the left of the office table?",
    "answer": "lamp",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "962b8661-a1bd-4536-b08d-49fc1634d058",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the couch in the living room?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "c5c06434-6fe6-4772-b7a6-d111f55fc7ad",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the bottle kept below the office table?",
    "answer": "blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "acdc1502-9c5a-422a-a712-4359f947ac24",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between office table and couch?",
    "answer": "lamp",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "4208a065-4c5d-4cea-a49a-3967d53cc6a8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the lamp between dining table and office table switched on?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "ae4069a3-cdeb-4e53-8db2-986725aab18c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the lamp between office table and couch switched on?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "741f1981-9b58-41ee-b783-c434bf113125",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I eat?",
    "answer": "banana in the fruit bowl on dining table",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "0a2df700-5c48-45be-a290-45bb44811362",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I watch a movie?",
    "answer": "on the monitors on the office table",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "1be3bd25-b738-4332-bbc4-a5364945d5d0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I take a nap?",
    "answer": "on the couch right of office table",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "f6388aa2-0b85-4d16-be44-4dbeca9c5374",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How should I clean up a water spill?",
    "answer": "use the paper towel on the dining table",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "ad1d1e19-42bc-4817-a87a-4e9826354724",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my medicine?",
    "answer": "office table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "908ee7e5-a682-427d-bfbe-7f30450a6e93",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "the table with the monitors",
      "next to the stack of papers on the table",
      "on the left side of the work desk",
      "next to the papers on the desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I find the pink bowl?",
    "answer": "dining table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "516d6b7c-2674-4f6b-9ee7-5e1f16f4d47d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/012-scannet-scene0785_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "to the left of the paper towel roll",
      "on the table by the window",
      "at the eating table",
      "next to the paper towel roll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is kept on the left side of the table?",
    "answer": "laptop",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "e0c78ad1-3c42-4973-ac92-cc88466d22f0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is kept underneath the table?",
    "answer": "trash bin",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "20554aef-f6cc-47c0-b9a4-7fe850fd3988",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is color of my toothbrush?",
    "answer": "White and blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "76a15ad3-96a9-4061-8195-ab8ae12aebb3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is color of my flower pot?",
    "answer": "yellow",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "f1a9ecf0-89c1-429c-bce2-8b5f862b6e3d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in front of the pile of clothes on the table?",
    "answer": "toothbrush",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "941531b0-77e3-4151-b8fe-eaf6f81a3fe0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the television switched on?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "f405628f-e87e-4bb9-9ea3-0b23efdcfbad",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door to the closet open?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "0fa26c3b-e79d-4aad-b534-607aaa34e8ec",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I arrange the clothes kept on the table?",
    "answer": "Hang clothes using hangers in the closet",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "088e4b66-160a-42c6-a65b-aa0a8967fb25",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I store my luggage?",
    "answer": "on the top shelf in closet",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "d3ff036a-23d9-48c3-a6d4-8cdc6082e0c3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where should I take a nap?",
    "answer": "on the bed to the left of the table",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "106afc4c-2e83-495c-8727-b031b72d5a7e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I find my toothbrush?",
    "answer": "on the right edge of the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "d1375469-87f7-476f-9aaf-a19422657943",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the right side of the desk",
      "on the desk",
      "on the black desk, towards the right edge",
      "on the desk, in a ziploc bag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I keep my pile of clothes?",
    "answer": "on the right side of the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "affd4e6a-1c28-44ec-bb2a-2de846198be0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/013-scannet-scene0720_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the desk",
      "on the right side of the desk",
      "on the black desk, towards the right",
      "on the desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the red object next to the sofa?",
    "answer": "vacuum cleaner",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "a0141ef9-a198-401b-be14-401182a3b27f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the sign near the stairs say?",
    "answer": "exit",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "fe05b434-7317-4502-96c1-0a02c8a56ea2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of sofa near the table?",
    "answer": "green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "018b71ee-f0d5-4774-87d6-f0a673a423ec",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is behind the vacuum cleaner?",
    "answer": "alarm",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "85adf68a-bf69-48fa-b612-6c10912e0f33",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between brown and green sofa?",
    "answer": "white table",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "41294b24-4e8f-4c19-a8d8-0ed1247090ec",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door near the sofas open?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "c8d5d713-9517-4ff5-8935-33688a433258",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there objects on the table?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "7a792e17-0d12-4ce3-8911-df2d3bb79087",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How should I clean the floor?",
    "answer": "use the vacuum cleaner",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "0762d773-14f4-4a4a-a517-b3b38735c254",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What should I do if I see fire in the hallway?",
    "answer": "activate the fire alarm",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "03145768-b1ba-4cf2-a537-9c334bfe5ce1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I use the stairs to go up?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "e621e982-d424-431a-acb8-4afa7a032d24",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave the vacuum cleaner?",
    "answer": "near the fire alarm",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "f1859dd5-0351-4bee-b9b0-5ae890984565",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "next to the fire extinguisher",
      "next to the sofa",
      "To the right of the couch.",
      "By the fire extinguisher."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the white single chair sofa?",
    "answer": "near the stairs",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "183b1bcc-63b8-470b-a0a7-0d2c3ebcd079",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/014-scannet-scene0714_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "near the stairs",
      "across from the balcony",
      "Near the railing.",
      "To the right of the staircase. "
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What object is in the middle of the floor?",
    "answer": "Shoe",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "70e43adf-2354-453d-9122-7cb61b5a4641",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What white machine is closest to the vacuum cleaner?",
    "answer": "Dryer",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "89adc84a-3e7a-4a14-9dcc-82f4f91c0afc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the room organized?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "9bd38301-7b12-4855-82e8-03ac7086dd96",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the room well-lit?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "47856f10-786a-4ceb-ad55-c583326c0dd0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where should I look for the other shoe?",
    "answer": "In the cabinets",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "019f71a9-46c6-4b0f-b909-fb520416173b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the tape?",
    "answer": "Above the laundry detergent",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "a7d5c6d2-0b3e-4136-9f3e-5741df739bc1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the dryer open or closed?",
    "answer": "Closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "957a3e81-3701-4261-9734-23234a1fc01c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the walls dry-walled?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "bb2b651b-c335-4c33-95d4-34b2b358e3ce",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to clean the floor?",
    "answer": "Vacuum cleaner",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "38fcfbac-c056-4f25-9c80-6de845696471",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do I store my shoes?",
    "answer": "In the cabinets",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "6756e56d-910a-4eaf-a3a4-bf71699614fa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the type of room?",
    "answer": "Laundry room",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "8f7c8704-c521-4c81-8caf-fe3e2680ef5d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the fire extinguisher?",
    "answer": "By the vacuum cleaner",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "74c7e66f-26da-4dcb-a331-1168b39c082e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/031-scannet-scene0787_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "next to the vacuum",
      "next to the vacuum on the green mat",
      "On the floor, to the left of the vacuum cleaner",
      "After you enter the laundry room, it's on the floor to your right after the first set of washer and dryer."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the pink box on the shelf?",
    "answer": "a Sketchers shoe box",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "9aa9815f-f10f-4fd3-824e-4e190b1a1722",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What''s the orange thing on the shelf to the right?",
    "answer": "a sleeping bag",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "d40eec6b-6d09-4bc6-9648-65f8e899965d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are most of the hangers?",
    "answer": "White",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "28348a31-3b08-4084-a7b3-057e160a9f8f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the purse hanging on the right side?",
    "answer": "Pink",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "9a25945c-5653-402f-909a-349792a31c7b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which side of the closet is emptier?",
    "answer": "The right side",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "70ca554d-cee2-47c9-8abd-a02e019c7656",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the drawers full?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "a21f3649-d8c9-4cb4-a26d-81e510aff2cf",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the laundry hamper full?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "3f6bd397-91f0-4ce8-8691-58e784b4bef6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I came to the closet to get something to take to the grocery store, what was it?",
    "answer": "The white tote bag on the wall",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "75f970c1-b092-4ca4-aa30-1763de31140b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use if my ears get cold?",
    "answer": "The furry earmuffs",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "056a109e-100c-4fbf-a85b-aa57d22679d8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the british shoemaker which has brown boxes with green lids and is known for durable shoes?",
    "answer": "Clarks",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "c2df1478-af13-4fa7-80ed-4bda7f4bae7e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my jean jacket with the fur collar?",
    "answer": "Hanging on the left side of the closet",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "b1da6ada-cdae-4433-9651-bafb974ebd07",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the left clothes rack",
      "between the pink and white shirts on the left clothe rack",
      "On the left side of the closet",
      "On the middle part of the left side of the closet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my black bag?",
    "answer": "On the lower shelf to the right",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "eb7b1a4a-fcad-418d-a9d1-a7d75434b2a3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/037-scannet-scene0763_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the shelf to the right of the hooks",
      "above the rack on the right",
      "Above the clothes on the right part of the closet ",
      "On the shelves on the right part of the closet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's on the top bunk but not the bottom bunk?",
    "answer": "A sleeping bag",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "62f3078c-03f5-4908-9079-c1ce15491699",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the room number?",
    "answer": "103",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "d1d0700c-225f-4b65-a787-8881fde764b7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the deadbolt",
    "answer": "Black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "fa04915a-aee0-4ec7-8b10-3728448d2efa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's on the wall above the top bunk",
    "answer": "a wood shelf",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "2c0e67a2-7625-40dc-ae37-00057910055a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's under the window sill?",
    "answer": "a backpack",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "35d8886d-c5ba-455f-b1a7-6fb7807a951f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the window open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "d8eabd13-48d9-4214-8148-f06ffae283ee",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the blinds more than halfway open?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "bf955503-883b-4aff-add7-c255460f2c68",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where should I sleep if I need to charge my phone?",
    "answer": "The bottom bunk",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "fe62db2e-6cd5-4a5f-9cda-304dfae8659c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are we in the city?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "daa15648-f82f-4ed7-bf87-43306dd0c5af",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What floor are we on?",
    "answer": "First",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b1440c06-44c0-4f6d-9547-0d8beb5e9c35",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the power outlet?",
    "answer": "By the head of the bottom bunk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "9a865041-4c98-4697-b84f-49770e0ad86f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "By the door side towards the bed",
      "Below the light switch next to the lower bunk bed",
      "On the wall where the door is, at the right of the entrance",
      "Between the lower bed and the entrance door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the light switch?",
    "answer": "by the door, just below the top bunk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "262deeba-e8a4-45c3-b5df-ee9746b067a3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/046-scannet-scene0724_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "By the door side towards the bed",
      "Above the power outlet next to the upper bunk bed",
      "By the door, near the upper bed",
      "On the wall where the entrance door is, on the side of the beds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the large object on the patio",
    "answer": "A glass table",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "ccf7e23b-7abe-47d0-8fee-131e9065e22a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is sticking out from behind the TV",
    "answer": "A powerstrip ",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "740ae41e-9ca0-471a-82e5-546db7842ac4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the water bottles?",
    "answer": "green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "632fe59a-2bb4-4e46-bd50-f6b40392ad54",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the patio chairs?",
    "answer": "White",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "e35875b7-5844-4f4b-9354-1ac985495869",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is hanging on the back wall of the dining room?",
    "answer": "a world map",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "0e369744-5723-4f41-a9e9-bb5185ccffd4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many dining room chairs are not facing the table?",
    "answer": "one",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "df42c730-83e0-4f81-b6a8-7023356efea4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are all indoor tables cluttered?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "c9f39725-8925-4e89-b4ec-222356847f1f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are all tables cluttered?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "215163b9-887b-41e6-9dfa-ebddf46e29e0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where's the most stable place to put my drink in the living room during an earthquake?",
    "answer": "Cupholder in the armrest ",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "15fd3498-0030-4f5c-b6de-43ee3f7e8c93",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the warmest place to stand?",
    "answer": "Next to the radiator by the kitchen",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "6332b74a-2515-4304-8f53-81232aceb466",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of windows does the house have?",
    "answer": "cantilever",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "50bc08f3-1963-4356-a033-de345b74aa4a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the cardboard cat scratcher",
    "answer": "right of the cat tree",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "474b38f5-3bfb-4d0e-974c-edd341b3d424",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "in front of the window",
      "in front of the window facing the outdoor table",
      "below the window",
      "to the right of the cat scratch post"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the printer?",
    "answer": "left of the china cabinet",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "6b48d4a4-b686-417f-b8e4-f0edcd6431fc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/047-scannet-scene0747_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on a low table against the dining room wall",
      "next to the china cabinet in the dining room",
      "on the table behind the dining table",
      "by the wall perpendicular to the television"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in the blue bin?",
    "answer": "Paper",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "07401190-3ebe-4cf0-a234-cfda55795868",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the top shelf?",
    "answer": "A paper bag",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "9dd79112-9b74-470d-abd1-1ffeebbac352",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many cups does the mr coffee make?",
    "answer": "12",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "cf59aff3-3a6d-43df-9e56-bee517336d05",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the bottom jacket?",
    "answer": "Cream",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "549c93e6-8d6f-460c-a971-53c14a1f74cd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many boxes are on the fourth shelf?",
    "answer": "two",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "3904a12e-13c0-4942-9577-75b4c53ac799",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is left of the trash can?",
    "answer": "recycling",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "58aba4ce-05b2-485c-a2de-6f313bbe641c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the boxes open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "06bde141-3961-4a70-a233-e37d971cd235",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the trash can full or empty?",
    "answer": "empty",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "ae502c44-7692-4a98-a1a1-2c7d2d823294",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shelf is for stuffed animals?",
    "answer": "third",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "5b441b79-fed6-4a60-ae82-26c637c9835a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where should I sit if I don't want to move anything?",
    "answer": "The floor",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "035062fd-f1e7-4ae5-be31-890ac991deae",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use as a pillow?",
    "answer": "The stuffed angry bird",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "f8240877-8fd6-4f7e-85b7-9f47cc1bc2ae",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does the person who lives here drink caffeine?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "2c898bd2-83f1-4e85-9eca-4ee3b94f52f5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shelf has research papers on it?",
    "answer": "Second",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "f7a58540-c121-4ac3-b95c-395cc26be3e4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "second shelf from the bottom",
      "second to last shelf",
      "The second shelf from ground up",
      "The shelf between the black boxes and the plushes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the jackets kept?",
    "answer": "on the chair",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "ffa767eb-1545-49e5-a0c4-fd733769715c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/048-scannet-scene0745_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the chair",
      "on the wooden chair",
      "On the chair",
      "On the wood chair between the shelves and the blue trash can"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is kept on the white table?",
    "answer": "computer",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "d76e6beb-7a4e-40eb-bb33-7c7185a070dd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which object is kept near all brown tables to their left?",
    "answer": "trash bin",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "82b4ae1a-8098-41ab-84de-5fd07899a77d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is color of the water bottle?",
    "answer": "light blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "0ef94e7a-431d-4f84-80d5-0ce3b26a5eff",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the computer mouse?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "7a96d76f-b71f-4e35-90c6-36f9ace86d8b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the right of the brown table?",
    "answer": "book shelf",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "08c65643-1f03-48fe-a6e8-c1d02ee4e027",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the left of maroon books on the top shelf of the book shelf? ",
    "answer": "blue books",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "b231fe4c-05f6-4872-973f-192b7808f555",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the window blinds in the room down?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "40d6009e-d083-4208-891d-a17e3d548947",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the computers on the white table switched on?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "f471c513-1b72-473f-9462-082cb0cab80a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What device can I use to send an email?",
    "answer": "computer",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "3e9974fb-8382-4f11-9755-538751e9a9be",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I get water?",
    "answer": "waterbottle",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "f8c33bd6-8250-47dc-bd48-ed2490528356",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which company made the computers on the white table?",
    "answer": "apple computers",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "be6227b0-23cc-43f4-af06-bf860f886405",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which room are these images from?",
    "answer": "library",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "678e3520-167b-468b-af3b-27d78daafd10",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the water bottle kept?",
    "answer": "inside the bag on the brown table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "6a86529c-d582-4c97-a05b-e205abcf041d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In the backpack that's on the wooden desk",
      "In the side pocket of the backpack on the desk",
      "In the water bottle holder",
      "In the blue backpack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the light from the ceiling lamps getting reflected?",
    "answer": "On the left side of the brown table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "10285eb2-f8d7-4fc6-8429-9d334744dea3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/100-scannet-scene0598_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the surface of the wooden desk",
      "on the surface of the brown table",
      "On the desk to the left of the chair",
      "To the left of the backpack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the white object on left side of the table?",
    "answer": "sewing machine",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "a3438480-9f46-41be-b844-9c7468315873",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is inside the basket kept on clothing rack stand?",
    "answer": "pillows",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b9702e2c-87a8-40d7-931e-28abbd4818dc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is my hat?",
    "answer": "brown",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "3add68e4-194b-4d28-9b41-d1980fb2c4ae",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the pillows?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "b5d424fb-fa1e-417d-9e35-093cad58376b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is above the sewing machine?",
    "answer": "lamp",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "58b620a5-2ac0-484f-a6b9-d44123bcca13",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we keep more pillows in the brown basket on the clothing rack stand?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "7c5a7a8a-faeb-42f4-80d7-267b70c04c20",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the drawers next to the clothing rack stand open?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "67e834f5-a987-49a1-9dca-64e407f46eaa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are both the lamps on the table turned on?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "1f7b15f1-f66f-41b7-a42e-81d610134c6a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": " How can I fix the tear on my cloth?",
    "answer": "use the sewing machine",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a79849ad-6087-40ee-bc5e-a446951550e9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I store my undergarments?",
    "answer": "in the drawers next to the clothing rack stand",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "6f032307-e1d4-463b-9867-ac53856fc068",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a person standing near the table?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "8e186284-0f79-42f4-b1af-096f8c9d47b9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I keep my pillows?",
    "answer": "in the basket on the clothing rack stand",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "5fa829d4-e353-4945-b25a-8f15421c7c04",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "in a basket on the bottom of the the clothing racket",
      "on the bottom of the clothing rack next to the boxes",
      "in the basket under the clothing rack",
      "next to the white boxes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my brown hat?",
    "answer": "on top of the clothing rack stand",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "a39b3be9-526b-4489-bfe5-a46f67ad2a93",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/101-scannet-scene0256_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on top of the clothing rack",
      "on top of the clothing rack right next to the stack of boxes",
      "on top of the clothing rack",
      "next to the lamp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which electronic item is kept next to the fan?",
    "answer": "charger",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "2f7ae8d8-efb7-4382-9eea-f9beee1d6a72",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the white and green object on the table?",
    "answer": "toothbrush",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "f0b13382-3545-4008-973a-bdaf47159381",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of my toothbrush?",
    "answer": "white and green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "6d9b2620-325a-4c12-8c3a-58aaa6068152",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which blue object is between table and fridge?",
    "answer": "recycling bin",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "7ae999ea-a082-43dc-9e2d-200efe91c03a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between the two fridge along the wall?",
    "answer": "door",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "0fba8ce5-d4b1-4585-ad22-9a4290907469",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the fan turned on?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "f938ed69-466e-46b0-91e7-aee308d409db",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the recycling bins empty?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "8bada0a3-28af-490c-9862-ade4968e86b9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I cool the room?",
    "answer": "turn on the fan",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "985001b3-3491-4fe1-9958-5da818eccf8f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I charge my laptop?",
    "answer": "on the desk using the charging outlet",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "bbb9566b-1a2c-4d4d-ad8d-bc9f7a5fedd8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the brand name of my shampoo?",
    "answer": "dove",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "52ee7f3e-fa1e-448b-9763-3984e23c3c1a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the brand name of my toothpaste?",
    "answer": "colgate",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "9441d028-29ce-42a2-9c2a-d67620b0a2a5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my keys?",
    "answer": "on the tabletop shelf",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "91f8e059-02d5-40c0-9488-d2b1a84e004b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the middle shelf",
      "on the shelf near the toothpaste",
      "on the shelf over the table",
      "next to the toothbrush"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my toothpaste?",
    "answer": "on my desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "31b7a8e1-e61b-4e0a-8e16-069776931797",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/102-scannet-scene0222_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the middle shelf",
      "on the shelf with the klenex",
      "on the work desk",
      "on top of the toothbrush"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is hanging on the hooks next to the door?",
    "answer": "bathrobes",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "5cbb9ad9-1929-4312-bc6a-cabf669043d8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which device is the person using to record the video?",
    "answer": "ipad",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "13069f9c-0540-43f7-9a2c-67292be59c45",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the cloth hangar?",
    "answer": "brown",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "eef57ae1-f959-4d38-bbd2-e182dcd64a7b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is color of the person's hair?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "c006256c-c0c8-47c2-9b05-4d8fbf75bd44",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can you see the lamp?",
    "answer": "in the mirror above the sink",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "3a2a65ca-8e98-4e84-ac36-d352131f3ca7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there water in the sink?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "8328906e-7bd0-4efd-a5b6-ad6c5e80403a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a cloth hanging on the cloth hanger?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "96563e62-a785-41bd-bb9d-d948e9580664",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What should I wear after the shower?",
    "answer": "bathrobe",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "c3362f10-cb6b-4e23-b2c7-3146ba2491cf",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I keep my shirt?",
    "answer": "on the cloth hanger next to the cabinet",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "f06b5a48-e918-4b7f-a907-2d26243c1f1a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which company made the tablet being used to record the video?",
    "answer": "apple",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "9c05eb03-b169-495f-8475-e46a1b070418",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which room is being shown in these images?",
    "answer": "bathroom",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "2bd14832-c870-40da-815f-9ecaf2bc26d5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my cloth hanger?",
    "answer": "on the hook next to the cabinet",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "2bf7aa3b-93bd-4d04-96a4-36c67476f49f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Hanging on a hook.",
      "On the hooks over the black table with the pamphlets. ",
      "On one of the towel hangers, in front of the sink",
      "On the hook in front of the sink"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my bathrobe?",
    "answer": "on the hook next to the door",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "9a38faf6-e4db-477f-aef8-dd393503c318",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/103-scannet-scene0527_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the hooks near the shower curtain. ",
      "On the hooks to the right of the white door.",
      "On the towel hanger near the between the shower and the sink",
      "On the towel hanger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which object is kept on the table in the corner?",
    "answer": "lamp",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "88a472ed-4344-435e-b80d-4c6f0db5ed96",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is color of the bridge in the painting?",
    "answer": "pink",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "dc4dc9eb-8311-4cd0-ad16-303441445164",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the shape of the table?",
    "answer": "round",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "c9fa0dcd-de50-4b46-8f4c-88400a41fa8f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I throw more thrash in the gray trash bin?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "2ad261f5-abca-4f27-a570-820c9c2f9760",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between fireplace and sofa along the wall?",
    "answer": "door",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "5d4a12ff-17f5-4a36-85da-2260c50c2bf5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "5132f0f2-df0d-4997-b5cd-f7c7c37b27fb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the table lamp switched on?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "85d55555-7954-4cc4-8fd2-0b22a0585b0a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I clean the room?",
    "answer": "use vacuum cleaner",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a0edd695-f005-4476-9417-3e0b7e3f2d71",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the right side of the bridge with red cap and white spots?",
    "answer": "mushrooms",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "39cd91e4-1abd-468b-a694-16fd68ac475b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you further brighten up the area around the table?",
    "answer": "switch on the table lamp",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "f04cdbb4-cf33-4639-80c0-94cc98c149af",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I see a girl?",
    "answer": "in the painting on the wall",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "6dd29e68-9b10-48f9-bdc8-a9d98c9ddb24",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the mural",
      "on the painting near the lamp",
      "in the painting, towards the left of it",
      "in the painting across from the armchairs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is vacuum cleaner?",
    "answer": "next to the fireplace",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "58cef625-96fc-4608-84fa-2fb93c4ef047",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/104-scannet-scene0616_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "left of the fireplace",
      "in the corner by the ac unit",
      "to the left of the fireplace",
      "in between the ac and the fireplace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the red object on the kitchen counter?",
    "answer": "coffee machine",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "90457509-f76f-4a0a-a7b8-ea095c58a0cb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black object behind the laptop?",
    "answer": "monitor",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "1d4d333e-c5e4-443f-833b-719cd8521387",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the vacuum cleaner?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "8e2458a5-22f6-4cb1-88b3-aec81d59452d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is color of the can next to the monitor?",
    "answer": "brown",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "8d02f444-6fe6-41ac-8a56-f923d81ab2c8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between sofa and kitchen counter?",
    "answer": "stools",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "6ee3c4cd-2aa9-4a45-b08b-f5c27264c672",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is right above the printer?",
    "answer": "bookshelf",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "a17d4fe0-bb67-4a52-ab83-5a1434eab2fd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the monitor switched on?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "433b1276-dd60-4551-8acd-fe77410d5b23",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the top drawer inside the closet open?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "ce8cb396-1fc8-4ff2-9c17-5a15fa4ffe4e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where should I sit if I want to work?",
    "answer": "black chair",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "aaf5eade-70c6-4aa5-98b0-9d0c76b85f0d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which company made the laptop?",
    "answer": "apple",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "1013266b-45cc-4e7e-97c1-f561dd007872",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to clean the water spill?",
    "answer": "paper towel",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "e3725196-ef52-49ac-bed1-f77db87bb0fb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the paper napkin?",
    "answer": "on desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "3e28dc6c-9885-433a-9f8e-1fc3f225c92c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In the back right corner of the desk. ",
      "On the desk near the bed.",
      "on the table with the laptop",
      "on the table next to the laptop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my laundry basket?",
    "answer": "near the bed",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "e8671320-81fc-4dab-bb22-2ef6e7289764",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/105-scannet-scene0207_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "At the foot of the bed.",
      "In front of the closet.",
      "on the floor right next to thee bed",
      "on the floor between the bed and dresser"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sports item is present in the room?",
    "answer": "basketball",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "45dfc5d0-db2a-4de6-8dc7-8a1100d719ba",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal plushie is on the top shelf?",
    "answer": "frog",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "c3c79f08-b726-4dc8-85b5-e1a2c3b363bb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the biggest robot in the painting?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "e087f46f-1fd5-4054-8db0-16b04fd8ab09",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color pattern is on the pillow? ",
    "answer": "checkerboard pattern",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "9a09d135-1e8b-4f55-811a-d2bac6af03b0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is behind the sofa?",
    "answer": "lamp",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "b7fc30fc-3014-4589-b6a0-23453cd26841",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal plushie is next to the family picture?",
    "answer": "teddy bear",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "3c4b5ee0-d307-42ab-ae09-52ac7c7ebb10",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the lamp switched on?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "82b0f464-09d1-4346-bbfc-9d7419605673",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the cabinet door open?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "ab6bfd30-72fd-4ef3-a703-0860e4457f78",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can the baby play?",
    "answer": "in the crib",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "b08736f7-c125-470c-b88d-9c3b148c2390",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can the adult take a nap?",
    "answer": "sofa",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "902e9bf6-2443-4b9d-b27a-837ab57381c4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this a room for an adult or a baby? ",
    "answer": "baby",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "f1013788-d7f3-4b3a-9c8f-ae037d6387f6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can you change baby's diaper?",
    "answer": "on the table next to sofa",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "35073455-9eae-423a-bba4-a58ce111af37",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the baby pictures?",
    "answer": "on the top shelf",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "1530fc16-2e49-4f5c-81ff-ff55226b07ba",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/106-scannet-scene0633_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the white floating shelves on the wall across from the crib",
      "on the white floating shelves on the same wall as the armchair",
      "On the shelf to the left of the picture of the robot",
      "On the shelf right above the cubbies"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the gray object in corner of the room?",
    "answer": "trash bin",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "94951922-fc1a-4c14-898d-0e5d6407de9a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the white object hanging on the red wall?",
    "answer": "whiteboard",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "e48cb9e2-a686-4833-ae3d-846a0be01921",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the wall with the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "e80efdc3-a589-419f-a59a-9afd824867a2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of non-black chairs?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "ce189a94-cd18-4868-a98b-9576e5db9128",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in front of television?",
    "answer": "black chair and red chair",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "f635297a-67d9-4a72-acbe-ff32dbe9fa43",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door open or closed?",
    "answer": "open",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "bb66d352-b33d-4758-b92c-8c71be7f4a1f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there any object on the conference table?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "2d53c160-e5f8-4615-9563-7899ec137c55",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I write math equations?",
    "answer": "on the whiteboard",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a2b9cef4-15a2-489a-b784-10019bd8f75d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where I can show my presentation?",
    "answer": "on the television",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a339748b-a292-48f0-ab32-e1ba945f9611",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which room do these images come from?",
    "answer": "conference room",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "46728774-e6bf-4b62-bd67-970e902a6f5b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where should I keep the pizza for the meeting?",
    "answer": "on the conference table",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "a0af16f9-2e25-4705-b726-d495b7e654c4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the charging outlet?",
    "answer": "below the whiteboard",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "e7c6095c-72d3-416f-9f3b-43f59f1aca3a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "below the whiteboard",
      "on the wall with the TV close to the whiteboard",
      "On the red wall bellow the whiteboard and on the white wall near it by the corner",
      "On the red wall bellow the whiteboard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is trash bin located?",
    "answer": "at corner of glass panel and red wall",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "5aac34c1-56b8-4781-a580-0c863ae22987",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/108-scannet-scene0354_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "below the whiteboards towards the windows",
      "below the whiteboard",
      "On the corner of the room, near the glass door and the whiteboard",
      "At the corner of the glass panel and the red wall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the green colored object on the table?",
    "answer": "calculator",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "134e115b-2956-457f-90e6-a1983a2ca2fb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the thickest book on the shelf?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "6ad7b496-d50d-4aa3-9b3e-2fa6d9c398b3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of square photo frame?",
    "answer": "blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "310af73b-9806-4e93-8916-c67b3bce5700",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on top of the calculator?",
    "answer": "red notebook",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "00e8e77b-6d1d-45da-bedb-ca2b0868b9ed",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between pencil and red notebook on top of another notebook?",
    "answer": "mobile phone",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "0b172e4a-7d92-4c4c-923d-9016fe12006d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does the orange water bottle have water inside?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "063fd978-bed1-45f2-9ee1-ba0cbbafd5be",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the large notebook on the desk open or closed?",
    "answer": "open",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "5f09a11c-f113-4224-8dfb-e024d47674da",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to speed up my calculation?",
    "answer": "calculator",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "d5e25c69-9bf1-4c49-a273-e7d8dd394b3d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am going out of the room. Which foot wear should I use?",
    "answer": "flip flops",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "4c2b7400-16e0-4123-9276-f46a4e847cd4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which religious figure do you see in these images?",
    "answer": "buddha",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b54dc085-5bbd-41f5-85c4-078585d5836b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What surrounds buddha's statue in the middle shelf?",
    "answer": "white candles",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "acd00cc4-f166-4f06-8cdd-a46a772e9134",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the hair brush?",
    "answer": "in the orange bag",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "0f05ae96-952c-48cb-ac87-0d6c66feb739",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "in the medicine case",
      "in the case on the desk",
      "in the orange bag on the table",
      "in the orange bag, towards the right edge of the table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my laptop charger?",
    "answer": "on the chair",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "e3a1393f-c49e-4666-b904-8ffc1ca8d0bb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/109-scannet-scene0648_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the chair",
      "under the desk",
      "on the chair",
      "on the chair in front of the desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the red thing under the desk?",
    "answer": "a cooler",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "3673c28f-e524-48f8-8756-a4bfdcded8a3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is plugged into the wall by the door?",
    "answer": "A roomba",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "4099caf7-210d-4e32-b9c6-8e23bf923503",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What colors are the toolboxes?",
    "answer": "Orange and blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "15025844-de18-4bbf-bae5-604c74c622b6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the armchair by the desk?",
    "answer": "Tan or brown",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "e0b667f8-4df0-4823-9f6f-c4bb8b7d7575",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in the corner between the french doors leading outside and the solid wood door?",
    "answer": "The desk along with a chair and a an armchair",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "bdcbfd8c-94de-43f0-9f6c-01ce0099787b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the large object in the corner between the french doors with curtains and the large couch?",
    "answer": "A piano",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "9dbc644e-d90f-4807-8bf4-54fc3bbc116a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the light in the room on or off?",
    "answer": "On",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "65be6312-4cac-4e5e-b5a3-78363d5069d6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there curtains drawn over the doors that look outside?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "38db515f-e13a-4276-b25f-09111024fc2d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to fix something and may require a screwdriver, where should I look?",
    "answer": "Check out the two tool boxes by the piano",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "b6bc27d5-2c3f-4146-89ab-be5af05f537f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "My friends and I need to work  and use the internet, what can I use?",
    "answer": "There are 3 laptops in the scene",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "dd5293d5-8795-4c03-bee7-72f4f337a47c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there anything I can use to carry a laptop in?",
    "answer": "The backpack on the ottoman",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "fbfb5704-7db7-4404-af47-bba6a24e1434",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of laptops are there?",
    "answer": "An HP and a Macbook",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "f3401156-5369-4ccb-be68-524a67a8290f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the blue coffee mug?",
    "answer": "On the desk, to the right of the laptop and by the printer",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "e3e35efd-965b-43ef-b6f9-3e65907e9581",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the desk",
      "next to the printer",
      "At the right of the desk",
      "On the desk, Between the laptop and the printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the tissue box?",
    "answer": "On the leather ottoman in front of the couch",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "e9348da6-12c6-43f0-82cb-65fee05c36ca",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/110-scannet-scene0050_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the ottoman",
      "next to the backpack on the ottoman",
      "On the leather Ottoman",
      "On the leather Ottoman, near the black backpack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats located on the wall right by the door?",
    "answer": "A hook",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "057c2863-ad20-41be-961f-0cb94072b365",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the floor mat?",
    "answer": "brown",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "13ca7431-0b00-491d-81ae-6b14a2b618b4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the toilet seat?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "d120fc5f-76af-4892-80c7-56637cb3bc74",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats to the left of the door when one enters?",
    "answer": "The shower",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "84db48de-f485-4f47-b954-ccb1d5732057",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats across from the mirrors?",
    "answer": "The toilet stall",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "72383fbb-5949-4970-8b5e-b7a186732c2f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the trash empty?",
    "answer": "No, its overflowing",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "249c1683-81b0-4d71-aa7c-4708fc3e9bf1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the shower dry?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "bdfdd853-dc78-49a4-b946-460447530303",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I dry my hands?",
    "answer": "Use the paper towels in the dispenser by the window",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "49dff9cf-97bf-427d-b83f-e35604654036",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I get some privacy when showering?",
    "answer": "Close the shower curtains",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "24d594b0-a305-40a0-9c53-c831dc8853bb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm not sure about the rules of the bathroom, what should I do?",
    "answer": "Read the sign behind the door titled \"Proper bathroom etiquette\"",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "6c28bf49-09a9-478a-8d95-050f9fb09e6b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Theres no more paper towels in the dispenser, what should I do?",
    "answer": "Swap out the roll with the spare one above it",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "c35752f3-3d61-403e-9f9b-20471a228114",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What room is the scene in?",
    "answer": "bathroom",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "934bf519-f8bc-44fd-baf7-4889c6a28551",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/111-scannet-scene0550_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "bathroom",
      "restroom",
      "Bathroom",
      "Restroom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats the yellow thing on the couch?",
    "answer": "a throw pillow",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "7e08669f-bbb4-46cd-a61b-2f58119567a9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is plugged in by the door?",
    "answer": "a heater",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "098ece70-032d-4ccc-9c5d-428c34b24b27",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the stapler?",
    "answer": "blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "acab5e16-338f-4e58-86b3-1242e2258dfd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the couch?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "7d69f1ef-73d8-4565-b52b-e54c0cc116a3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on each side of the wall where the door is located?",
    "answer": "shelves",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "be3ec633-cf6e-44dc-b70b-fa9bcbd28971",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is across from the couch?",
    "answer": "a short bookshelf",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "ffa34918-7ff9-401b-8114-c489e9fcdb62",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it daytime outside?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "bacd9518-93ac-409e-a79b-2f40a3e0ece4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is anything hanging on the wall hooks?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "49276a81-6d39-4b37-8d89-ad25210debf9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need some energy , is there anything to drink?",
    "answer": "Yes a can of redbull right in front of you when you enter the room",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "07035e88-b9e3-4cac-a5cb-b3e7e335b68e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What logo is visible in the top shelf to the right when one enters?",
    "answer": "Red Bull",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "7f266d5d-9a08-46e9-8bf4-7a9fb0b974ad",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats visible on top of the desk divider to the left?",
    "answer": "A small golden trophy",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "57a47d40-792d-46f7-a3dd-de8fef82af1d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wheres the tape?",
    "answer": "On top of the shelves of files",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "8d6629a6-e5d8-4603-8c66-d8a6a816b8a6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on top of the file ",
      "on top of the file cabinet close to redbull",
      "To the left of the red bull",
      "On the left side of the desk above the files"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When one enters the room, which side is the research poster on?",
    "answer": "To the left",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "be7911dd-6e1b-43e8-b09d-a56125ad6ecb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/112-scannet-scene0591_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "left side",
      "towards the left side of the person entering",
      "on the wall to the left",
      "above the black couch on the left"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats the blue thing on the chair?",
    "answer": "a duffle bag",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "25406fb9-39d1-4a9a-9800-ac882ae70f86",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the duvet cover?",
    "answer": "dark green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "5178b12e-a949-4788-bbfe-36ecd035cec8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the shirt on the closet door?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "ffa331f6-ac1a-4f57-b31b-737165b012f4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What cleaning tool is across from the stove?",
    "answer": "a vacuum cleaner",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "95d1c129-ce47-4ba4-b052-8156f8a56d6f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What piece of large furniture is next to the open window?",
    "answer": "a bed frame",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "d8e924b2-17c7-467b-b192-320925e7039a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the window by the couch open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "b6a0c99d-e03e-4fd1-bdc3-17e89271b98b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the bed unmade?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "78e0eadf-cf7f-4797-998f-59916d6a7e4a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need some flavor in my meal, do you see any condiments?",
    "answer": "The soy sauce, sugar, or salt on the desk",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "e01e51db-73d9-47f3-8756-128b5d8d89af",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to carry things to class, what can I use?",
    "answer": "The two black backpacks by the couch or the blue duffle bag",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "edf52424-2116-42b1-bd1b-f029ade2ec9f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to prepare a salad?",
    "answer": "The wooden bowl on the desk behind the monitor",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "28135ee1-f64d-4813-b430-09b15c7790ec",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are m laundry baskets?",
    "answer": "at the foot of the bed",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "f6c0acac-13c6-4c64-ae0f-553346c73126",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/113-scannet-scene0207_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "at the foot of the bed",
      "next to the bed",
      "On the floor, near the bed",
      "At the foot of the bed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats under the sink?",
    "answer": "Trash bin",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "5e1b9e7e-db01-4f98-8333-ee251c04e32c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats the yellow thing aginst the wall?",
    "answer": "A caution sign",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "5c927376-5d34-4228-955c-c0ce67a6d40e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the counter?",
    "answer": "beige ",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "21c2be19-48f2-401a-aef3-c86156eb80ed",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the piece of paper by the door?",
    "answer": "bright green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "9092a6da-481e-4a98-b20a-2a8e8a3b9a28",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the outlet?",
    "answer": "Behind the soap dispenser by the sink",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "a7798fc4-becd-4816-918b-3be114fdea69",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the sink turned off?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "d4caa082-a63e-46e3-9caf-e029c8c70979",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the trash full?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "371dc542-9854-4cfc-b8cf-a16fac37cb5e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm feeling cold, is there anything I can use in the scene?",
    "answer": "the jacket on the counter",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "c0f9c7ae-cf3c-49b0-be64-34971d65dd7b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I let others know the floor is wet?",
    "answer": "Stand the caution sign over the area that is wet",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a49ac3ba-e308-42a6-8b2e-fb0c73f6613d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there any natural light I can use  to check my makeup?",
    "answer": "There seems to be light from a window within the room",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "8278f446-fd5d-4044-b5eb-6cf1cf10c9c1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I turn on the sink?",
    "answer": "Lift the handle ",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "1c89b1e8-b690-4bdf-8f73-32e4d3f27d60",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you seen my shampoo?",
    "answer": "Yes behind the jacket on the counter, to the left of the sink.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "0ae5ddbe-a98f-42dc-ab53-07ec0f9bfec4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "To the right of the toilet paper",
      "On the left side of the counter close to the wall",
      "Yes, it's on the counter near the jacket",
      "On the counter, between the sink and the paper towel dispenser"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the extra toilet paper rolls?",
    "answer": "Behind the paper towel dispenser, stacked on the counter",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "afbe9506-e865-4c66-865f-268c935403cc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/114-scannet-scene0084_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In the left hand corner of the counter",
      "To the right of the paper towel dispenser",
      "On the corner of the counter, near the towel dispenser",
      "Behind the paper towel dispenser"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the colorful object on the bed?",
    "answer": "a blue towel",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "6bac9434-3a35-4ecf-821f-9214d1089bd0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on top of the sweatshirt in the suitcase?",
    "answer": "an iPad",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "0cd06eb4-7e2e-4985-8b10-2b7437dc8c63",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "what color is the carpet?",
    "answer": "green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "378795a0-33e3-43bc-abd1-65c1371db7e4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my cellphone?",
    "answer": "on the desk, to the left of the laptop",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "b0370ddd-3bf8-4a77-ab83-54a727d189a7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a walkable path to the desk?",
    "answer": "Yes, but watch out for the shoes on the ground",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "99571a75-6e17-4ba2-b4e4-0d7b6b74179a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the curtains drawn?",
    "answer": "Yes, the white ones are but not the blackout shades",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "d58639eb-be6f-4c0f-a186-bd5cabca70e7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the suitcase open or closed?",
    "answer": "open",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "22295a94-7153-465e-a66b-9a9d9b5b08f8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use for entertainment?",
    "answer": "the laptop, television, or ipad",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "ed73c96a-8ef3-427a-ae19-2d4d2da3636a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I have a seat?",
    "answer": "Either on the green bench, the blue chair, or the bed",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "643ba7ee-6385-49d9-be44-9638849f9045",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to carry things for a quick errand?",
    "answer": "theres a purse on the desk and two backpacks by the suitcase",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "20e9fe5c-dd12-4bab-aed8-194dae180adc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you seen my purse?",
    "answer": "Yes its on the desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "a3074ccb-6653-44c7-9334-374cbcde6d78",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "it is on the desk",
      "it is on the desk next to the laptop",
      "on the table with the laptop",
      "on the table infront of the tea and coffee bag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my wallet?",
    "answer": "next to the laptop",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "6646f817-4825-4f05-a209-bb75950069d9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/115-scannet-scene0046_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the desk",
      "to the right of the laptop",
      "on the table right next to the laptop",
      "on the table near the laptop and infront of the mouse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the multiple machines visible in the photo?",
    "answer": "printers",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "a2130e5d-6b76-4a8e-bc8b-c55c9119f7ca",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is directly by the entrance?",
    "answer": "A trash barrel",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "90d38f22-8815-4dd2-b1fd-12f177d64404",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the sign behind the advil?",
    "answer": "pink",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "aaa3ce91-bcab-4c1a-90b4-ae0c33d8a268",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What size is the room?",
    "answer": "small",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "12a6a639-cdc0-474a-a84a-1313a17cb89c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats under the table?",
    "answer": "cardboard boxes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "eb4ef411-56bf-406f-92ef-9004dd7775f6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the light on the black printer on?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "90cd464d-9184-4772-9130-f931a05fa5e8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I organize and store some papers?",
    "answer": "Use the organizer tray on the shelves",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "c37ae971-9ea0-404d-a2da-a635e8f7ee7d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to disinfect my hands?",
    "answer": "the hand sanitizer on the counter",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "7baa5f0f-642c-4cf0-84f7-2f3cff16f251",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there any medicine that I can use to reduce swelling and relieve pain?",
    "answer": "Advil on the shelf",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "49585c58-cc40-48c2-860a-5d58a5a7c048",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What might I need if I'm sneezing a lot or have a bloody nose?",
    "answer": "the kleenex on the second shelf",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "19015e68-6ff5-485b-a427-517b0074b264",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the paper cutter?",
    "answer": "To the right of the printer on the desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "f3d503d5-6906-464f-b434-22fd02447f44",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/116-scannet-scene0077_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "To the right of the printer.",
      "On the table with the grey scanner. ",
      "next to the printer on the desk",
      "next to the printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black object on the table?",
    "answer": "a desk phone",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "c0795364-b3e1-4e46-b685-ac535c4bc47d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the white object on the table?",
    "answer": "a roll of paper towels",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "92cff5f9-03f1-4aef-a22c-9fe9ebbd979f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the desk phone on the table?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "75020e8d-abe6-4e64-8d30-37caa4032ef6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the chair behind the table?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "e994eafc-0185-4783-a924-71c3f14f03df",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in between the door and the table",
    "answer": "stack of bins and paper box",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "ae1e5043-c875-4155-9908-d5fc8f54ed29",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the black chair on the table?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "604fccd0-48b3-4ba5-8508-3a3526b2161f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "bfbe82af-7830-430a-82ac-939ad58f9a00",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the room messy?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "cd4f9d78-25fd-4dac-a2f0-86f7af957f6d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I call my friend?",
    "answer": "use the desk phone on the table",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a87bddf4-9672-49bc-890c-dc57788e4e01",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I sit down and rest?",
    "answer": "in the chair near the table",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "0c9ff956-2520-4529-b20d-541ed596bd97",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I spill some coffee on the table, so what can I use to clean it up?",
    "answer": "there is a roll of paper towels on the table",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "fd26fc7f-bbcc-446d-a1a8-4bc7354af16c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I saw someone that is fainting on the floor, what can I do to call for emergency?",
    "answer": "use the desk phone on the table to call 911",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "88a218b2-b8e2-4b67-8f77-7cd47707fc8a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my paper towels?",
    "answer": "on the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "eac83b7b-61e9-4b23-8449-f4ee6221a72d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the desk, in front of the chair",
      "On the desk, near the phone",
      "on the desk",
      "next to the phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the stack of white bins?",
    "answer": "between the door and the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "7ae2afc8-01c4-4019-ba12-00cdb038a548",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/120-scannet-scene0684_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Enter to the room and look at your right",
      "Between the door and the desk",
      "to the right of the desk",
      "next to the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the brown object next to the closed door?",
    "answer": "a paper box",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "da31a414-1a7e-408f-85a1-68d45f7b6997",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the background color of the paper that says \"class X\" on it?\" ",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "fe0b868e-92e3-484f-aa8b-550e732519a8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the US postal service bin?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "953dbacd-8afe-4f33-983f-815c0c752c54",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a door that is open?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "b2c61fb2-be00-4f70-8880-17d028f0d1d3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the tabletop (with US postal service bin on it) clean?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "72553b2f-45e5-44f6-99ba-80e104c6de28",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door near the brown paper box open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "7185fe27-149d-4283-88ad-3653214367b9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I make a copy of my passport?",
    "answer": "use the photo-copy machine on the table",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "982536c8-1bb0-444c-ac9a-14f63317f4b7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have a couple of mails that I would like to deliver through USPS, so where should I put them?",
    "answer": "there is a USPS bin on the table",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b88abf34-0446-480a-9c39-0a7e9d4e7ea5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the US postal service bin?",
    "answer": "on the table with the fax machine",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "b866979f-7056-41cd-ba13-6fa6ec1e519c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the left side of the counter",
      "on the counter next to the hole puncher",
      "across from the door",
      "on the counter to the right of the stepping ladder"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my brown paper box?",
    "answer": "in front of the closed door",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "cbfbe85b-eb4d-43aa-966b-bcfda2fae507",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/121-scannet-scene0462_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "in front of the closed door",
      "next to the green bucket",
      "to the right of the green bucket",
      "On the floor behind the printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in the center of the room?",
    "answer": "a ping-pong table",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "fdb4bea3-6ae5-4358-a324-532029d7271a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is next to the wooden chair (near the electric outlet)",
    "answer": "a backpack",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "7ff27c74-935c-4e1e-83e5-0c964e3cc39d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the sofa in the room?",
    "answer": "dark green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "50e54518-481e-4f37-a3f6-f023d7f42bb1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape is the table close to the sofa?",
    "answer": "square",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "f389f406-95a4-4cf3-9167-8b81e18d0d5c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in between the two orange stools?",
    "answer": "a high table",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "7458f812-e388-4196-96ef-57b3c194c9fa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a ping pong ball underneath the ping pong table?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "672c0ce3-f6e0-4474-b572-abcfbca1a9c5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door open or closed?",
    "answer": "open",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "6c9a4608-82f6-464f-94e3-adcc241ead99",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the ping pong tabletop clean?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "ccbae04a-858c-483d-b87a-f0d66a80a395",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am so tired and I want to rest somewhere.",
    "answer": "you can lie down on the coach near the room exit",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "b56d03e0-7762-40ce-861b-bdc86a4b4527",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in the big painting next to the ping pong table?",
    "answer": "dandelion",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "6cd140e9-f477-4799-a6e6-cadc921990c5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "If there is a fire emergency, what should I do?",
    "answer": "follow the exit sign and open the door with the sign exit on it to escape",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "1cfe0ea7-c0fd-4625-be0e-f1e6f2ba53ba",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the large painting with a dandelion?",
    "answer": "on the wall",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "568afdc9-e2a0-4ec6-8293-f7ae43c8e279",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the left wall if facing towards the door ",
      "On the right door if entering the room",
      "far from the entrace",
      "next to the ping pong table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the wooden chair?",
    "answer": "near the electric outlet close to the sofa",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "4ee1cb14-6687-4c3c-902e-ff38fe883bf4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/122-scannet-scene0647_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "By the wall Near the sofa",
      "By the wall at the right if entering the room",
      "to the left of the entrance",
      "next to the booth seating"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the red objects on the shelf?",
    "answer": "a stack of plastic cups",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "e783e004-3bbc-44d9-a264-3f6e3becd0b7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the orange objects on the floor?",
    "answer": "a stack of traffic cones",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b7c76f16-bec9-4215-9713-cdcb75aaf9f2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the stack of cups on the shelf?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "ee7ded98-c926-47e7-bca4-5398cb394e4a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the two colors on the traffic cones?",
    "answer": "orange and white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "50780d08-48a2-45c7-b05e-4c0f9f511fd7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there room on the top layer of the shelf?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "1c2b0364-2b79-47c5-86a2-2c3c7e6a480c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the ladder folded?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "6756db97-f9ad-4c9e-8f65-40b6e558e193",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I clean the plastic cup?",
    "answer": "in the sink",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "51aec2d4-9bc8-4f01-92d0-14ed4aa27c5d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I reach the top layer of the shelf?",
    "answer": "use the ladder to climb up",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "78c3648f-c8f8-4de8-92fb-12ca2e21e1d2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't have a water bottle, so what can I use to drink some water?",
    "answer": "there is a stack of plastic cups on the shelf",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "bc4465ed-dd94-4eec-9a9f-54b5c906b1fb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "My clothes are all wet, so what should I do to dry them?",
    "answer": "use the clothes hangers near the sink",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "a689a632-8117-4e41-8e19-101668a8d5cd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I put my ladder?",
    "answer": "next to the door near the orange traffic cones",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "9a63d1fe-1f60-4f29-aa59-2033a3b16217",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "right in front of the double doors, leaning against some metallic equipment",
      "next to the orange cones on the floor",
      "Its near the entry of the room, at the right if walking towards the door",
      "Its near the entry of the room, at the left after entering the room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my plastic cups?",
    "answer": "on the bottom layer of the shelf ",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "bbc7ab7f-7150-4df0-9b03-921218ee66d5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/123-scannet-scene0412_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the first level of shelves, right above some black crates",
      "on the shelves, across from the sink and countertops",
      "On the bottom shelf",
      "On the shelves"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black, square-shape object on the table?",
    "answer": "a monitor",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "7905e99b-38ae-40ab-8a8b-de520157b0f5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the wall behind the mini black fridge?",
    "answer": "a white board",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "556f4095-f6b3-49bb-8c9c-7811c2a3cb19",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the table that has multiple monitors on it?",
    "answer": "brown",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "77ed7b7e-3bb0-4b35-9df1-4da9c5f2239d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape is the mirror?",
    "answer": "round",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "b5fd796d-b299-40e5-9271-b1b2cde4c366",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there black plate on top of the black mini fridge?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "bf24221b-2f48-4dd6-b4ee-6132c384bbf7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a poster roll next to a white mini fridge?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "358927b1-dd2c-4f64-b754-05d15476a1dc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the table (with multiple monitors on it) messy?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "52ce09d8-8549-42f7-b3dd-a12700c8b60c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I work on my essay without using papers?",
    "answer": "Turn on the desktop and connect the monitor to it",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "6835ef85-efb2-4c80-b224-b373e3e33fc0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I store some fruits so that they last long?",
    "answer": "in the black mini fridge",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "54da25a7-ff70-4467-874c-3a1b034814f1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the brand of the monitor where there is a keyboard in front of it?",
    "answer": "DELL",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "c79ae994-7ac2-441b-ac16-c19b7e3a5a40",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "My laptop charger chord is not long enough from where I sit to the electric outlet. What should I do? Is there something in the room that can be of help?",
    "answer": "you can use one of the extension chords on the ground",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "4c82287d-7310-45d8-9211-cfa21f352abf",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the keyboard located?",
    "answer": "in front of one of the monitors on the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "6ef2cc09-f7ce-4818-8be5-a719f5e2ca8f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "right next to the mirror on the table",
      "close to the monitor  ",
      "in front of the widescreen monitor",
      "in front of the bigger monitor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the mirror located?",
    "answer": "on the table leaning against the wall",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "cf72f8cf-18be-4813-bb90-60477209299c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/124-scannet-scene0131_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the table ",
      "on the table close to a couple of keyboards",
      "on the table, right above the drawers",
      "on the table, to the right of the small monitor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black object on the bed?",
    "answer": "a remote controller",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "43ce5442-125d-4272-aa48-17748dde37bc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the pink object?",
    "answer": "a jacket",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "6a28c652-a68a-4716-91e6-578ab1224f8a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the hoodie on the arm chair?",
    "answer": "grey",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "8f313348-3bfe-4657-a9a6-e64da1a5f921",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the shape of the painting on the wall?",
    "answer": "square",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "7c4456e4-0209-4638-bea2-11387a050cad",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between two monitors on the table?",
    "answer": "the piano keyboard",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "71385df3-5afd-4925-b855-15c3ffd87813",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there room on the table work on a laptop?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "05aba429-6388-4a1b-ad39-e256e8b237c3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "78302470-73e8-4860-92f2-93c47b428dc3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the drawers open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "67f96d5b-9087-4a56-80cf-9bdd9122ae1e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I warm myself up?",
    "answer": "put on a pink jacket in the room",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "87ac2b53-0b0a-402d-b5f1-9134391aa84c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is the box of bottled water on the ground?",
    "answer": "Kirkland",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "39f540b6-b206-4a9e-9fad-583c449de6c6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the book with the yellow color in the second plastic bin (from the top) in the plastic bin stack?",
    "answer": "BARRON's AP Physics C",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "44ea3c68-4e15-412e-a56b-a75e66791287",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the box of bottled water?",
    "answer": "on the ground near the three tiered drawer",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "83ff1f40-6b46-47a0-980e-bf3e8e09a00a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the floor",
      "on the floor under the tv",
      "in front of the tv",
      "to the left of the entrance of the bedroom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the piano keyboard?",
    "answer": "on the table next to the bed and a stack of plastic containers",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "4bf0f902-bb29-42cc-9bab-b57de7847ede",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/125-scannet-scene0426_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the desk",
      "on the desk next to the monitors",
      "next to the bed",
      "next to the stack of clear boxes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the white object near the peephole on the door?",
    "answer": "a map that shows the emergency evacuation plan",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "0a268fbb-c24d-40ec-a824-cf63efe5c4c0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What objects on the ground near the door with the peephole next to the short bench?",
    "answer": "two pairs of shoes",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "565fab38-557a-4e64-80c0-e21aaefb144b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the pair of shoes closest to the door with the peephole?",
    "answer": "brown",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "4e6fcd0e-096c-482a-9420-6849ce73207b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape is the sign/map on the door with a peephole on it?",
    "answer": "rectangular",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "c3b87229-ae61-4843-a880-d4f861626507",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there some room to hang more clothes?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "1a9563fb-9aa3-4a1d-bae6-935fdafc18d4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are between the door with a peephole and the short bench?",
    "answer": "two pair of shoes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "0b28af1a-322e-4c62-95ed-e25d040059c3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are two doors in the scene. Is either of the door open or closed?",
    "answer": "both doors are closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "320a0be8-1bfc-462c-9d3e-8be5586d9f17",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there any clothes on the cloth hanger?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "d75dd87e-5b59-4418-9646-6e5d2a84b13a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I dry my wet clothes?",
    "answer": "hang them using the wooden cloth hangers between the two doors.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "5bce4102-fbca-4d26-b2cb-0688c64ff734",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to see what is on my face. What should I do?",
    "answer": "there is a mirror right on the left of the door with a peephole ",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "3d5f493f-3ae8-4681-830c-cf6081f5c1c7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my shoes?",
    "answer": "right next to the door with peephole on it on the ground",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "c7399516-76ad-4506-adba-f9caa4f96483",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/126-scannet-scene0574_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the floor, near the door and the bench",
      "On the floor",
      "by the door with the deadbolt",
      "next to the bench"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the blue object on the chair?",
    "answer": "a backpack",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b736fcaa-15e5-48b3-a672-319f94af8055",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object on the table?",
    "answer": "a water bottle",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "a74956e0-1377-47b7-9a90-37731bf86e64",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the backpack?",
    "answer": "blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "de02cdce-36b4-4aa7-a3e3-5c8bc4e78ed6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the water bottle transparent?",
    "answer": "yes, with a blue body and a white cap",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "80ef0262-0420-4af5-85a0-f352b35df678",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are on the wall below two wooden frame windows?",
    "answer": "two electric outlets",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "6e09d6fb-62fe-4b08-ad87-f81d475405ff",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the tabletop clean?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "68c7e76d-ce72-4727-a90c-3e503529e01e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door closed?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "688a56b8-8cde-49ba-981a-ab21d301ed35",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do I throw away food packages?",
    "answer": "in the trash can right next to the door",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "ed46a30d-f749-4eba-a9aa-d908a6515a60",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't have a vase, so what can I use to display flowers?",
    "answer": "there is a water bottle and the cap can be removed so that the water bottle can function as a vase",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "a67994b9-e3ca-421a-9000-b6f2712d0d4d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my backpack",
    "answer": "on the chair",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "b899b89c-8dbf-45c7-a73e-40f4e6bbd436",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the chair",
      "on one of the chairs",
      "on the far wooden chair",
      "on one of the doors near the windows"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my water bottle?",
    "answer": "on the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "237b591c-fc08-4187-843e-c54aad388de8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/127-scannet-scene0578_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the table, right in front of the backpack",
      "on the table",
      "on the window side of the desk",
      "in front of the chair with the backpack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the red object on the washing machine?",
    "answer": "a foldable laundry basket",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "53581c1b-e73a-4599-86aa-fde90c4e1ead",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the orange object on the water sink?",
    "answer": "laundry detergent",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "0d7cb464-017b-43c9-a1e5-04cfae60cc17",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are colors of the floor tiles?",
    "answer": "white and dark green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "3b151322-ac8f-475c-90c0-841008e44006",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the foldable laundry basket on one of the washing machines?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "5d63aace-28f8-461a-ad49-b353384ca751",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is below the white plastic storage bin?",
    "answer": "two microwaves",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "89ab17cf-edfe-4f0d-8c5f-eab797207efe",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there washing machines with open doors?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "58a3e024-23b4-41ca-9ee5-caf3c2db0cf6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the red laundry basket folded?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "499bf969-8d75-4380-b60c-aea4a6ae47e5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I get some pop drinks?",
    "answer": "buy some from the vending machine near the corner of the laundry room",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "9b776c41-58e6-4fb4-83cb-1cf05958502b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the brand name on the brown paper bag?",
    "answer": "Levi",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "2d03b6db-8e36-4fa5-be69-111d380a5eef",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is the bottled drink displaying on the vending machine?",
    "answer": "Pepsi",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "57768def-46e6-413c-8e63-a26738376ec8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my paper bag?",
    "answer": "on top of a black plastic bag near two microwaves and a plastic drawer",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "20d5875f-4634-4db8-8f89-75986306a850",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/128-scannet-scene0678_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On top of the trash bag. ",
      "Next to the empty clear drawers.",
      "on top of black pastic bag ",
      "on top of black pastic bag near a green bucket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the white object near the end of the table that is close to two monitors on the wall?",
    "answer": "an instruction sheet on how the AV system works",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "396436f6-b7fd-48c7-a4b6-1c2c596fd25e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between the two monitors on the wall?",
    "answer": "a video camera",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "98896b18-c580-42b9-a2fa-45c2ebdeb2d6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape is the table?",
    "answer": "rectangular",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "5686072e-064f-4a05-ac06-5af3ba316b34",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between two monitors?",
    "answer": "a video camera for the video conference room",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "61260253-5136-42ba-a3db-43d59899b53a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there room on the table work on a laptop?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "5fd7fef5-2821-4a05-b15a-a886faa2c6c7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "7b033898-d039-4fe1-a43b-cb3ceaf74400",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the monitors on?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "44a4483a-7921-4edf-b531-a94a6da53ecc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I turn on the video conference system?",
    "answer": "read the instruction sheet on the table and use the remote controller on the table",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "5f53b669-55d2-4885-acac-1d40f36015eb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am thirsty, so what should I do?",
    "answer": "there is an empty glass that can be used to fill some water",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "f43777f1-6e4d-4ba2-9516-60982d2e0c16",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my glass?",
    "answer": "on the table near the microphone",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "df714f0e-e908-4a6c-adcd-8eaf53e91e6d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the conference room table",
      "in the middle of the light brown table",
      "Next to the blue wire",
      "On the light brown table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my remote controller?",
    "answer": "on the table near the instruction sheet",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "934ce134-edbd-4840-8047-4c0d7593b62a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/129-scannet-scene0575_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the conference room table near the white paper",
      "on the table towards the monitors",
      "To the right of the blue wire",
      "On the table to the side near the wall with the television"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is placed on top of the stack of chairs?",
    "answer": "basket",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "8fc06e98-2de5-444a-a91f-c2096408ffd5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/130-scannet-scene0696_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located in the center of the room?",
    "answer": "tennis table",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "adeee329-01aa-4b91-98a0-4823fd8810b6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/130-scannet-scene0696_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the box on the tennis table?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "541f9e4f-1729-4038-85dc-06ae5a35dc1f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/130-scannet-scene0696_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there monitors in this room?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "8a513e64-2bc4-4b7a-8904-01aba5b6c2da",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/130-scannet-scene0696_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How to dry the clothes?",
    "answer": "on the drying rack",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "2b8f0752-2767-4322-810b-4c4f2992b4ad",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/130-scannet-scene0696_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What components of the computer can be found here?",
    "answer": "monitors",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "f3888439-d03b-4401-a883-b2b9485fa322",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/130-scannet-scene0696_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the mattress located? ",
    "answer": "on the floor",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "299c78da-6c6a-4dca-99e6-cfbcac54392d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/130-scannet-scene0696_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Leaning on the bookshelf.",
      "Near the head of the table.",
      "On the floor, in front of the table",
      "On the floor, laying in the big furniture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the red box located?",
    "answer": "on the tennis table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "c1bbf838-e06a-446d-a91d-924b62fa41b3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/130-scannet-scene0696_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the ping pong table near the bookshelf.",
      "In the corner of the table.",
      "On the table",
      "On the table, near to the entry of the room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What can be found at the edge of the bed on the right?",
    "answer": "tv remote",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "752937e0-2152-4c99-9fee-937cc7e7c77f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located on the left from the table lamp?",
    "answer": "clock",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "e9040703-f2c7-4ac0-a6f7-261f44be393b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape of the brown pillow on the beds?",
    "answer": "cylindrical",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "c4ad33e1-a6e9-46ce-af84-23f1399fec39",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is color of the table lamp base?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "34440422-5884-4070-99fa-44b79bee7170",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there room on the nightstand to put a book?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "6d662db3-1de5-47af-b2aa-ced6a3c7bb85",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the beds made?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "fd29e918-e7df-414e-a48c-7fcf8a201bce",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the nightstand clean?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "8141f14c-5677-47e1-9716-ca0fe1d98b90",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How I can made a note?",
    "answer": "use the notebook on the right bed",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "2dbd9c54-8dc3-4eca-b900-6e1dd1ccd2fc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where I can read a book?",
    "answer": "in the arm chair",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "8e8cc828-fc17-4d91-8bc4-696cb7802767",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of entertainment available in the room?",
    "answer": "TV",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "e3990bd6-5e91-4a1c-91d2-dc6c5c0e0813",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to change the TV channel?",
    "answer": "use the tv remote on the bed",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "c429e90b-6e20-492d-bf27-63c662325659",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is clock?",
    "answer": "on the nightstand ",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "2763f93f-d48a-4542-8a34-c016cbed805f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the table between the beds",
      "on the table next to the lamp",
      "on the bedside table in between both beds",
      "next to the lamp on the nightstand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is tv remote?",
    "answer": "on the edge of the right bed",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "77ce83aa-b651-489e-827d-47d9eeb9cb48",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/132-scannet-scene0645_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the bed to the right",
      "on the bed near the window",
      "on the bed next to the laptop",
      "on the bed that's closer to the window"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located on the counter on the left?",
    "answer": "a printer",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "d08b3e22-3b0f-4d9a-915b-81d9556cf548",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located on the left from counter?",
    "answer": "a trash bin",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "6702a7bf-8d68-422f-8d9e-98c633ce9182",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the counter top?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "dff9dc3a-4d00-4bd6-95b3-18a36e549eff",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape is the counter?",
    "answer": "L-shape",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "ed4930f6-d661-4769-96e5-1fe22ea03cfb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the trash bin empty?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "d6423493-2f38-481e-856e-933f0746a84e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the table on the right clean?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "cefb9ac6-48c6-4990-916a-ea5f064295ee",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I get a water?",
    "answer": "from the cooler",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "86b77fd5-5d96-425a-9d1a-56fca347254b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can be used to get a cooler water refill?",
    "answer": "the cooler bottles rack",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "6adf4d05-9932-45c9-8e2c-73e8e60f3445",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where I can get a sheet of paper?",
    "answer": "in the printer's paper stack",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "233f7385-951e-4dd9-9fce-45d6465ff92d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of room is it?",
    "answer": "printing room",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b2f4ba91-22af-4797-9690-2ed0ef51ba6c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I left my dolly?",
    "answer": "on the left from the large printer",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "797c7e52-eaf8-4d38-a068-867f2a57e248",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In the middle of the copy room.",
      "Next to the table in the copy room.",
      "on the floor right next to the large printer",
      "on the floor leaning against the wall close to the large printer in the corner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my paper cup?",
    "answer": "on the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "608cbb12-849c-4a54-8b11-0a54c828c66e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/133-scannet-scene0704_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the table to the left of the water dispenser",
      "On the table next to the ream of paper.",
      "on the brown table close to the water cans",
      "on the brown table between the water cans and large printer "
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located on the chair?",
    "answer": "clothes",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "f00170c7-2bf6-4fac-881a-7505a04a999e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is hanging above the bad?",
    "answer": "a tapestry",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "4fd93501-a723-428d-a227-6100af6180c9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the game console on the table?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "9bc60545-6323-44aa-a797-2b104ef6bf54",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color of the clothes on the chair?",
    "answer": "blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "0ebea1eb-2a04-4daa-b783-8967f3d0232d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": ": What is in between the pillow and the wall?",
    "answer": "the plush toy",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "b5928051-adaf-49ee-8f16-2b809b5aa117",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there room on the table to put a book?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "359102e5-42c0-4deb-8df2-7a591b41c25c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Has the bed been made?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "85ad26c6-bd23-41ab-ad22-fc5190ec4e90",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the table clean?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "d4a9a244-2d9a-4ee3-a29d-202154838f15",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "How I can be entertained?",
    "answer": "play on the game console",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "9cc36f4f-750c-426c-a3a5-ae003e926a81",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "How I can write a code?",
    "answer": "on the laptop",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "6b6899e1-bd12-4d98-8fb8-fbdbc347a9a2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in the tapestry?",
    "answer": "mandala",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "c5be3792-7d9b-4b93-8a4d-fe943c696307",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my pen.",
    "answer": "on the bed",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "5dd8abfb-29e7-45c7-a32d-da620cf493a7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the bed.",
      "Near your pillow on the bed.",
      "on the bed",
      "on the bed in between the pillow and comforter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my gaming console?",
    "answer": "on the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "5b9a8c8e-b2ba-4a40-b80a-636dea351a58",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/134-scannet-scene0695_03",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the edge of the desk.",
      "On the desk. ",
      "on the wooden desk",
      "on the left edge of the brown desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located on the right wall?",
    "answer": "a whiteboard",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "11f04053-7f62-4beb-a0ee-3b26e1bfe406",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What leans on the wall on the right?",
    "answer": "a poster",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "02a02496-904f-456a-9032-d88af21fc6fa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the flag on the wall?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "96748f3c-b4c7-4b42-b7b1-fbc7ace75374",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the shape of the mirror on the table?",
    "answer": "round",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "eea0c67f-eeb6-4895-843b-753d7d62c44a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there room on the whiteboard to write something?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "538f6a98-804d-49f7-999c-83b0b2839359",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the whiteboard clean?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "70ebe785-480d-4269-b1ee-14b148956074",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the monitor on the right desk connected to the desktop?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "0926a44c-6440-4822-adb6-cf5d7962b412",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where I can draw diagram?",
    "answer": "the whiteboard",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "3e81102b-3741-4b10-8c66-07a4de67f85e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have a macbook, how can I connect it to the monitor?",
    "answer": "using the adapter on the desk",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "16ed2144-9409-45c3-a4e1-9bdcf506eab5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am going to the scientific conference, what should I take with me?",
    "answer": "the poster",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "a5b37d32-b0c4-4573-9085-e69cc8297e13",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the mirror located?",
    "answer": "on the desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "7c053159-37ea-4c82-8251-6388decabbd1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the table resting against the wall",
      "on the table right next to the keyboards ",
      "In between the two monitors",
      "Leaned against the wall on top of the desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where bottle with red liquid is located?",
    "answer": "on the desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "648168c1-daba-4e54-a29c-00c1e83a22b1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/135-scannet-scene0131_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the desk right next to the small monitor",
      "on the desk right between the book and the small monitor",
      "below the poster with the building",
      "to the right of the white book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the blue object on the desk?",
    "answer": " a backpack",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "bde5e2f5-2f71-4af2-b235-866d9e9c2704",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located on the white desk?",
    "answer": "computer",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "90f23451-bbad-4ef9-8094-9f39f3fcdc07",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the desks with computers on top?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "83d2dbc2-3dae-43b5-99b8-b827bd49dff5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is color of the chairs?",
    "answer": "gray ",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "dd7bce27-21e6-4e6e-bd11-406eac7f7093",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located in the center of the brown desk?",
    "answer": "glass screen",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "5f175d5b-90f5-4457-889e-91d06e227fb7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": " Is there room on the desk?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "e74a9d1c-e75b-49bc-ad66-f4b1e485b755",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the white desk clean?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "889ae40d-e3f8-4649-8744-7e278699c29d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where I can get something to read?",
    "answer": "on the bookshelves",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "e4ac7c05-a94b-4929-994a-7c0623bd4367",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to charge my laptop, where can I find a power outlet?",
    "answer": "on the brown desk",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "32d69796-26fb-4467-8f17-786ebf010ece",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why glass screen is needed?",
    "answer": "reduce noise",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "95e2802f-af82-4688-a7ab-ad56708cfec8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How I can get access to the internet?",
    "answer": "using computer on the white desk",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "52835ce7-7c9f-4717-ba8d-ed77461ccb90",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my backpack?",
    "answer": "on the brown desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "7c56866d-e112-49e0-85a5-b120848f22c6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "By the grey chair",
      "On the table across from the computers",
      "On the brown table",
      "On the brown table near the chair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are computers located?",
    "answer": "on the white desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "a8e8eee2-b234-4172-9485-7c33eaf0055d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/137-scannet-scene0598_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the desk to the left of the windows",
      "to the right of the door",
      "On the white desk",
      "On the white desk near the wooden wall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What can be found on the corner of the table on the left?",
    "answer": "the remote",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "8f1cf88b-cf1a-4b9b-bbc9-83fce2df43cd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located on the front wall?",
    "answer": "the blackboard",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b9384377-414c-4742-91f7-bde8d2635301",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is color of the office chair with wheels?",
    "answer": "gray",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "2c4c1beb-e285-44d6-84ce-4716dee56916",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the shape of the table on the right side table?",
    "answer": "round",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "9e5aa952-66ca-4f51-a107-456dafa74304",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the floor in front of the blackboard?",
    "answer": "the wire",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "ef569a31-9c3b-4361-aed3-be7e9467e5c8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can be found on the left side of the clock?",
    "answer": "the window",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "85ae1917-eca9-43d5-83cd-3c850442757d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the blackboard clean?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "54939c10-6881-4a92-a85c-27ff435aaa25",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the table in the center of the room clean?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "27256d20-448b-4607-b504-c486af19ddd5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can draw an animal?",
    "answer": "on the blackboard",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "05541e69-cce8-4ed6-8e30-399b437c8bfc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How I can share the presentation materials?",
    "answer": "using the remote and the projector",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "020f8677-ed5e-40cd-9406-56b33622d5c9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the remote on the table being used to control?",
    "answer": "the projector",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "0aac4f49-8fff-4e34-8f86-285592c15cad",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my remote?",
    "answer": "on the table on the left",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "bf506312-d5f4-4553-8a58-7b415f9a8390",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "At the end of the table",
      "It's on the table, near to the blackboard",
      "by the blackboard",
      "on the large desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the gray office chair?",
    "answer": "in the corner of the room",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "4f765634-429d-4ec6-a9a2-d3f350bee0c7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/138-scannet-scene0500_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "It's on the corner of the room, near the blackboard and the window",
      "On the corner of the room",
      "by the window",
      "to the left of the blackboard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located in the center of the room?",
    "answer": "a ping-pong table",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "577d32c7-3233-4a98-a3f4-eb08e796a343",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What orange furniture is in the room?",
    "answer": "a barstool",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "55d33dd0-946d-498d-b426-ef193c2460b9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the barstools?",
    "answer": "orange and silver",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "62772c2f-8c0d-4937-a6df-3ad2730a688d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the shape of the sofa?",
    "answer": "L-shape",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "671b27ae-6163-4f29-a9be-ec178ef0deea",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located between two barstools?",
    "answer": "table",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "3e89fffe-1ced-412d-8096-59fbdc4a1386",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is located between the sofa and the chair?",
    "answer": "a backpack",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "154d2dfe-5d4b-4e48-8904-42ae648433a4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the table near sofa clean?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "cf338176-0f53-499c-a134-50a4a832ea79",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the ping-pong table new?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "da56e4ab-8354-434d-b894-9b6aa2611ea8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I play with my friend?",
    "answer": "using the ping-pong table",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "d7160347-b3a1-4511-90ab-26a20da5bbf2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How a couple can sit together?",
    "answer": "in the bar table and barstools",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a59f87e1-f591-4486-9f67-7b6e9bb4c546",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why green signs with light are used?",
    "answer": "to mark the exit",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "8c6e4087-1888-46c9-b971-854e9d4d70f0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the backpack?",
    "answer": "near sofa",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "27d14f84-ada8-4a66-becf-301486fbb7a0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the floor",
      "on the floor near the seating area",
      "near the sofa",
      "near the wooden chair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the orange cone?",
    "answer": "near the exit door",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "61bea689-3869-4a4a-9f75-5018b8df5dab",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/139-scannet-scene0647_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "near the fire alarm",
      "next to the exit door",
      "in the hallway",
      "outside the ping pong room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the large white object on the table next to the right wall of the room?",
    "answer": "Printer",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "5d0efe22-db6d-4d6f-b9a8-3fcd5b29fd11",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the dial color of the clock located on the shelf?",
    "answer": "White",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "483d6ff5-e95e-428e-8990-606767755752",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the scanner located next to the shelves?",
    "answer": "Black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "3c872380-37e2-47ec-9b64-f46dc9224953",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is directly in between the large white printer and the room entrance closest to it?",
    "answer": "paper recycling trash bin",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "199fc658-9cb8-431b-a087-211d797b8838",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there sufficient space to add a queen size bed to this room?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "f5dd281b-fe55-4441-a57d-cc209213cad0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the lights turned on in this room?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "c6d9f5b9-dbed-4781-aac6-8171520408b3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the entrance door to the room open or closed?",
    "answer": "open",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "ced848d4-9022-4811-9fca-8343d5824bfb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I throw away paper waste in this room?",
    "answer": "Paper recycling trash bin",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "5a0068ea-51e3-41cc-8c42-aa0d89295bf7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What appears to be the main purpose of this room?",
    "answer": "Printing",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "62999995-eba7-4ac7-936a-998dc0f13caf",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is behind the small white printer on the counter?",
    "answer": "Windows",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "98a93f9e-7274-42f8-8b44-f367cc379f92",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is displayed on the walls that don't contain shelves?",
    "answer": "Scientific posters",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "dd41d385-6228-46ab-a7c0-e0d2f25e299a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the small back trash can?",
    "answer": "On the floor, next to the entrance door.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "50ff385e-1232-4683-a685-533022a3ed3f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "next to the door",
      "to the right as you enter the room",
      "to the right of the door",
      "against the wall across from the window"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the small clock with a white dial located?",
    "answer": "On the middle shelf, towards the right.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "3e618dcd-a620-48d4-9dd5-45e1b6d5dea5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/140-scannet-scene0077_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the middle shelf near the window",
      "on the middle shelf above the counter",
      "on the second shelf",
      "over the black printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is immediately to the left of the refrigerator? ",
    "answer": "stove",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "226ff028-f02d-468d-aabf-033e8895fddf",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/141-scannet-scene0651_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is the color of cabinets in the kitchen?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "871de0ed-d536-47a2-bde7-c5bd9eba1bf0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/141-scannet-scene0651_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "what color are the refrigerator handles? ",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "5d8f83b8-a2bb-444c-99ff-3cac2895e6c1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/141-scannet-scene0651_01"
  },
  {
    "question": " Is there room on the counter work on a laptop?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "a467e7d5-bd72-4edb-9b61-f7d633fef774",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/141-scannet-scene0651_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the kitchen countertop clean?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "9a0ec462-d85d-4d29-aaf1-4d9f0db24d5f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/141-scannet-scene0651_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the kitchen sink tap open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "1dfedfc5-04e6-4e73-99e5-3725b3d5c58b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/141-scannet-scene0651_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use in this kitchen to warm up a burrito?",
    "answer": "stove",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "452d61cc-07d6-49d2-a59d-6cbb8412429c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/141-scannet-scene0651_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you see a trash can in this kitchen?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "c3b3c036-f06b-4193-9035-09eb075a05ea",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/141-scannet-scene0651_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the blue bin?",
    "answer": "on the kitchen floor",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "ecf3c464-7d62-4daa-8ce1-37032d585f96",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/141-scannet-scene0651_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Tucked in the corner by the outlet.",
      "Near the drawers in the kitchen.",
      "On the floor",
      "In a corner on the floor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the green object on the desk?",
    "answer": "Whiteboard marker",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "d7cb9f77-ab44-43e8-952e-1df8254ae13b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the white object on the floor under the desk?",
    "answer": "Power strip",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b2ed5cdc-65a2-4b3a-86d2-4c9a5ff6eca9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color whiteboard marker do we have?",
    "answer": "green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "847274ec-56d4-453c-9790-8fd745076921",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the filing cabinet?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "3336b4ea-964b-431f-8dfb-c0e5329f4a7f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "If I'm sitting and working on the desk next to the hand sanitizer, where would be the whiteboard in relation to me? Answer from front, behind, left, right.",
    "answer": "behind",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "77979338-3f99-47a7-ac4d-ca46357ae1fa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the computer monitor on the middle work desk turned on or off?",
    "answer": "It's turned off",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "f6ba1915-3f0d-4d2f-95e6-ce18f19093ed",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the computer monitor on the work desk closest to the whiteboard turned on or off?",
    "answer": "It's turned on.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "d66336d8-2c8d-4717-9c89-870f85f04473",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the filing cabinet closest to the white board open or closed?",
    "answer": "It's open",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "6da85dd4-341c-4d29-9528-b55ffa5e0680",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to quickly explain a mathematical equation to people in this room. What can I use?",
    "answer": "You can use the whiteboard. There are markers nearby to help write.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "ef4e055b-7a80-4f9b-a86a-3163026ab5e2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I just sneezed. What can I use in this room to help protect myself or colleagues from any diseases? ",
    "answer": "You can clean your hands using the hand sanitizer on the filing cabinet.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "530c279f-0ebf-433d-9ef0-f4d2d86da682",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of work place setting does this place correspond to?",
    "answer": "University lab or office",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "526b9ed9-c409-4cb9-b859-93f41f4c752a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm looking for my book that I was reading yesterday. It has an orange book cover. Do you see it somewhere?",
    "answer": "Yes it's on the filing cabinet at the far end of the room.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "9099d1e1-2376-417c-b1cd-516ad5f1f386",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Yes, it's on the cabinet near the desk",
      "On top of the cabinet at the right of the desk",
      "above the filing cabinet",
      "to the right of the desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I just came from outside and need to clean my hands. Can you find something useful for it?",
    "answer": "Yes, there is hand sanitizer on the filing cabinet in the far end of the room.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "98bbe1fa-34a1-4c0e-b276-ca90742cdbe4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/142-scannet-scene0653_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Yes, there's a hand sanitizer on top of the cabinet",
      "There's a hand sanitizer on top of the cabinet that is furthest away from the whiteboard",
      "hand sanitizer",
      ""
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the green and yellow object on the desk?",
    "answer": "eraser",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "82162992-04d4-4178-8ead-6782761f3b7c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object with a blue display?",
    "answer": "telephone",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "7783e5f2-7c21-44ac-86cd-fda634635de8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color marked was used on the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "c5d6763a-9859-484c-86c6-2b73814b5173",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "what color is the work desk?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "47ce1cef-9602-4837-b422-e278993610c9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the room door open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "f4564aea-aafb-40d6-8407-65ce04349d0f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the computer turned on or off?",
    "answer": "off",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "e4245364-bc3d-4ed8-84e4-492df400c345",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I store all the papers on the desk securely?",
    "answer": "In the filing cabinet ",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "c8f1f36b-1b75-42f5-a959-bcb88b70e2bd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of room is this?",
    "answer": "Office",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "6e547b1b-9ab9-4a5d-b1ec-0cd8073ca365",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my cellphone?",
    "answer": "on the work desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "d0186859-7e18-4fbb-b651-bc38b64b324d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On your desk.",
      "Near the pile of coins. ",
      "on the table next to the keyboard ",
      "on the table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my water bottle?",
    "answer": "on the floor",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "024300a0-100f-427d-b643-d05b7768f894",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/144-scannet-scene0700_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the floor under the rolling chair.",
      "On the floor under the backpack",
      "on the floor below the chair",
      "on the floor below the chair with the backpack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the white object on the floor?",
    "answer": "trash bin",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b9a8a5a8-ad09-4412-ad05-5191bbfca956",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object is on top of the work desk?",
    "answer": "shelf",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "a50613c0-8edb-4fe0-84c6-988d0b0ad98e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "what color is the task chair?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "b74494f1-d1be-4dd8-a643-8f80dbe41139",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is the color of the window curtain?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "d6d2c525-e841-49a7-9e5d-b1cb75f17751",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "what large black object is in between the bed and desk?",
    "answer": "chair",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "3e15212e-ad0e-427a-9360-98449383c860",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "which object is closer to the window, the bed or the trash can?",
    "answer": "bed",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "a1612351-7a02-4c8c-914b-9a074c6f2325",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the closet door fully closed?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "8f8966b6-7b62-4aa0-bcdf-b69312c153bf",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the window curtain drawn in such a way to block sunlight?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "087b4e0e-74bc-4440-aa2f-50f7c1496d88",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I make this room darker?",
    "answer": "Installing a darker color window curtain",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "3b3a4b73-b47d-4742-b75f-3480e0563acb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "The closet is full. Where can I store a suitcase in this room?",
    "answer": "Under the bed",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "70b5d159-2547-4336-844f-fd50fa974bce",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the two main functions or purposes of this room? Why did you arrive at those conclusions? ",
    "answer": "Sleeping, since there is a bed. Working, since there is a task chair and desk.",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "c7045ff9-71b6-47d8-8815-8a18e927dd64",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What main objects are missing to successfully sleep in this room?",
    "answer": "pillows, blankets",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "c19a83ae-ee50-4e15-81d9-9838b30024a2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the two-tier shelf?",
    "answer": "on top of the desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "9be4c0df-1754-4341-b1ac-afe3c503e8cc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On top of the desk.",
      "On the left when you first walk in to the room.",
      "above the desk infront of the chair",
      "on top of the desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the trash bin?",
    "answer": "on the floor, near the closet",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "caa77055-4305-4e7e-939d-a00b52a943df",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/145-scannet-scene0193_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "To the right of the closet.",
      "On the floor near the ethernet ports.",
      "next to the cabinet by the wall.",
      "next to the cabinet close to the power outlets in the wall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the yellow object on the chair?",
    "answer": "backpack",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "2eaa2322-26f3-4d90-b36c-db69768b78ac",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the transparent object on the white coffee table?",
    "answer": "jug",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "fa127e93-b1ea-47a0-bd74-100da0b93a65",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the sectional couch? ",
    "answer": "Orange",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "e5f8a674-532d-4dd9-a101-1f7626837582",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the backpack?",
    "answer": "yellow",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "e5692e2d-d135-4917-83e6-1a8712b3ddd0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "If I'm sitting on the couch and the TV is directly in front of me, where would the work desk be located relative to me? Answer from front, back, left, right.",
    "answer": "right",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "9eb97c49-f0a7-4543-bd8d-4771797bcd27",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What white object is in-between the couch and TV stand?",
    "answer": "coffee table",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "6429730d-cf37-44e9-94b1-f531a8d8e9e6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the TV in the room turned on?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "63e92254-c74e-4120-b928-4a13d4af1d21",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is anyone sitting on the couch?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "893c624e-c8e2-4afc-a724-f23934ed537a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where would you suggest placing a computer in this room?",
    "answer": "on the work desk",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "3c21d0ab-6036-4766-8bcf-599b12b80280",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm thirsty. What can I use in this room to pour myself some water, and where is it located?",
    "answer": "jug on the coffee table",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "e624827e-fc89-475f-88f6-ccd4aaaac866",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which English alphabet is decoratively displayed in blue color near the work desk?",
    "answer": "m",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "7540a030-2aec-451d-8579-855fdae1cc62",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm looking for my yellow backpack. Where is it?",
    "answer": "On the chair",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "0a1fbfe2-43aa-418f-9f9e-205da59445ee",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the desk chair",
      "on the desk chair to the right",
      "On the back of the righthand chair.",
      "Hanging on the office chair by the desk."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm looking for my comfy pillow. It has an image of a clock on it. Can you find it?",
    "answer": "on the sectional couch",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "c227470f-7d64-4de3-89b4-5e2b73679fa2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/146-scannet-scene0518_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "it is on the sofa",
      "it is in the corner of the sofa",
      "It's on the orange couch.",
      "It's in the corner of the couch. "
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which object is closest to the AC unit?",
    "answer": "Tissue box",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "e46e1b38-b285-4382-a3a7-696077f772d3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black colored object on the floor next to the bed?",
    "answer": "backpack",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "beb00aa9-f908-4633-9f63-b8bcc37d4c8a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the frame color of the artwork in the room?",
    "answer": "gold",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "a4dd1c33-d705-4c29-9987-0e2140650c54",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the hairbrush? ",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "ceaa311c-5689-4cc4-81bd-3a92e7d7bb57",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "If I were working on this desk while seated facing the window, where would I find the AC unit in relation to me? Answer among front, back, left, or right.",
    "answer": "right",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "80ba0af2-59a0-42c1-82b2-08b9e3851164",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the large object between the AC unit and wooden desk",
    "answer": "bed",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "3c2f39ec-36e9-4a88-b9f3-2f01613dcb0b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Has the bed been made?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "65ba162a-3b37-4243-9c5f-ed5cd434f95e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the window open to let in light?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "8f495a8c-473f-422f-a489-fb9ac3654a0f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "It's a very hot day outside. What can I use in this room to cool it down?",
    "answer": "AC unit",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "d0198e47-78e4-49f1-af83-ba10dbd2c526",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I take the toiletries on the table on an airplane carry on luggage?",
    "answer": "Yes, they appear to be small bottles and in clear plastic bag",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "9bf13104-dc4a-4a50-adef-27f190382d5f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave my wallet?",
    "answer": "On the wooden table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "f5898a9b-1a89-4bc9-8283-43677cca290f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the desk",
      "on the desk near the window",
      "Next to my keys",
      "Behind the water bottle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the tissue box?",
    "answer": "near the window AC unit",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "ee015c5c-6248-4457-9394-d1289b6c998f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/147-scannet-scene0699_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the radiator",
      "next to the a/c unit",
      "On top of the radiator",
      "By the window"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the title of the book on the coffee table?",
    "answer": "Sailing",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "a81fef48-9967-4ca2-a3a8-5a5392c78656",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the brown elongated object on the rug?",
    "answer": "poster tube",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "d7f763d9-5c61-40c1-ac80-47c79bfb3e6d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of shoe rack?",
    "answer": "cherry wood",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "72140295-4d39-4392-a5dd-8ab22c86d95e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the background color of the framed photo near the entrance?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "eede4405-ab07-40df-9e60-0ce4460da2a4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "If I am sitting on the couch and looking directly at the book shelf, where would the shoe rack be located relative to me? Answer from among front, behind, left, or right.",
    "answer": "behind",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "5f92e442-8c74-43ea-b84c-37493feb638d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the bookshelf empty?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "1a159113-328a-4f85-876c-3b05f77ea04d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this room tidy or cluttered?",
    "answer": "cluttered ",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "9e46f6c7-b820-47fc-b62a-3ca31e21c40a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is depicted on the framed photo next to the wooden door?",
    "answer": "Gandhi",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "6fa9f3f3-576b-4a6c-8f81-d395ff3db054",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the gray colored pillow?",
    "answer": "on the floor, near the couch",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "49a03cab-013f-4fad-b072-1892e5067374",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "under a stack of blankets.",
      "To the right of the colorful chair.",
      "To the left of the bookshelf",
      "Below the window"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the book on sailing located?",
    "answer": "On the coffee table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "056ce5a4-f054-4e72-a4ce-4966fdd79571",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/148-scannet-scene0203_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the coffee table.",
      "On the table in front of the couch.",
      "To the right of the rolled up poster",
      "To the left of the grey couch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the largest object on the dresser?",
    "answer": "TV",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "6df3bcb4-495c-44d1-ac95-588927459ebe",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the room door handle?",
    "answer": "gold",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "6d6be7ec-48b4-4f96-a6e4-382a0433b917",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the bedsheet?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "639d327d-b697-4571-a708-9a884f993f42",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What large object would I see first when entering the room through the door?",
    "answer": "Bed",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "093164ee-ba7e-4482-a8fa-b3bcb0b6f727",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "If I'm viewing the TV straight will sitting on the bed, where would the window be located relative to me? Answer from left, front, right, or behind.",
    "answer": "behind",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "30663e52-1655-4831-a610-433c177d9063",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Has the bed been made?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "80a53d17-e686-4746-89e6-e0b759bf3980",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the window blinds open or closed?",
    "answer": "closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "a3ebe222-885f-4069-b7ca-8441381333ec",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "In a typical home or apartment, what type of room is this one?",
    "answer": "Bedroom",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "3d7fefc5-4359-4d9b-87d5-4eca5405d354",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can the yonex bag in this room be used for?",
    "answer": "storing and transporting rackets",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "730872a7-0f97-49c4-b988-8f7d827a3522",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm looking for a bottle with a red cap. Where is it?",
    "answer": "on the dresser",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "330096e1-304d-4b9d-aa5d-9a057682faef",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the right part of the dresser",
      "On the dresser, at the right of the TV",
      "to the right of the tv",
      "near the bike pump"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm looking for my Yonex racket bag. Can you find it?",
    "answer": "It's on the black chair next to the floor lamp",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "5f8e141a-90b8-4e36-a1f1-de5d876201db",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/149-scannet-scene0426_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Yes, it's on top of a chair, above two towels",
      "Yes, it's on the black chair",
      "in front of the tv",
      "next to the lamp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the green object on top the 3-drawer white cart?",
    "answer": "An umbrella ",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "239e8ab9-bab4-4cb2-8fda-3680d37b8edb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What clothing is the teddy bear on the purple quilt wearing?",
    "answer": "A red hoodie",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "45986175-0d27-4ac1-af21-13b50b45e9a5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the cap of the red water bottle?",
    "answer": "Pink",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "53171175-2b63-4fe5-90f1-0f6fe72d88c0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is under the small red book?",
    "answer": "A calculator",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "b089a6db-d46b-49b6-b774-217f74479d23",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the red bottle empty, full, half-full of water?",
    "answer": "half-full",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "e73e8300-86d0-47b8-82bc-e4aeddf7203b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the MacBook open or closed? ",
    "answer": "Open",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "cea31de3-d3dd-4f73-a88f-3f94c11dc6b2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can be my footwear in the room if I want to take a shower?",
    "answer": "the black slippers",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "7ea448d9-1079-4cc1-8ff2-57857cf61fb5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which water bottle should I go for if I'm thirsty?",
    "answer": "The red water bottle with pink cap",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "73d71e2b-e29b-4b26-ab38-a8f05cb71ca5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I keep a dog in this room?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "e5498ed0-430e-40d4-9d6c-20d61473379e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Today's really hot, can I find something to wear on the bed?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "4452055f-2c7e-453e-8926-e1dbb8db50ff",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the big red book?",
    "answer": "On the first level of the brown cabinet",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "cf2e76d8-f2e3-4d12-8ad5-53ddf6e68dfb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "right next to the buddha statue ",
      "in the lower level of the cabinet ",
      "On the desk, near the buddha statue",
      "On the desk in front of the chair in the first level of the shelves"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the plastic bottle?",
    "answer": "On the brown table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "0808f052-79e3-4bde-bbb9-608077c86095",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/150-scannet-scene0648_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the table right next to the bed infront of the lamp",
      "on the brown table right next to the bed",
      "On the desk",
      "On the desk, at the right of the chair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the table next to the door?",
    "answer": "A red backpack",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "70a0c836-f572-4454-8264-506c0c3c0461",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the mattress?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "3e02d0fe-366b-4cf6-a468-be7930f2dbe0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I stand in between my bed and my white desk?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "340c57fb-54b5-4a5e-b53f-77a9db08dfb3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I put something big under my bed?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "898ac9c5-1ba8-432f-aed1-f59a59f7e295",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door open or closed?",
    "answer": "open",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "8cac31ac-ac39-42ba-a3bc-74fa8ec19db1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the garbage bins full or empty?",
    "answer": "empty",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "a94091c5-6a43-4560-aaa9-95738ada32cd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the black chair easy to move around?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "d2dac362-782f-4f04-a154-530c81735357",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many choices do I have if I want to recycle something?",
    "answer": "2",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "69a8bdfe-4e7e-4f1a-9e64-48781276ddfc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there anyone living in this room?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "34903a96-bc9e-4de6-ba55-059b1329d4fe",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many roommate will I have if I live here?",
    "answer": "1",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "20144df8-0b9b-443c-b3ff-61a470621ed6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my backpack?",
    "answer": "On the white desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "df1efdd6-00f5-4f17-936f-c6d600f48fc0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/151-scannet-scene0217_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the white desk closest to the entry door",
      "On the desk",
      "on the desk across the bedroom entrance",
      "on the second visible desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many chairs are there in the scene?",
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "c5972a01-f323-4915-820f-e13a698204b4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object on the floor and near the door?",
    "answer": "A garbage bin",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "21cb1ce5-db23-4e0a-bd42-93524817c121",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the chairs?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "24aa7b71-ecd0-461e-94d5-0e4e0fc78a9c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two colors of the wall?",
    "answer": "blue and white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "0fd50c36-32f8-4a08-bee3-b5387db8be6b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the garbage bin closer to the door or the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "the door",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "c07b6d96-9a0f-40c2-b9f5-a3aee4801a76",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the chairs relatively close or separate from each other?",
    "answer": "close",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "6c668cea-e8ca-4213-a7d1-1f9e442cbc02",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door open?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "54e161d7-e60c-4960-8f08-e8cec9c99c41",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the chairs tuck under the table?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "c474bd96-ca4f-4e61-bc9c-bf0f776e7e25",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the wall that has ports for my laptop's internet connection?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "dba97e50-5486-4b7d-a69a-a2295fca49d1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there something that I can use to throw away my garbage?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "99227ff9-2583-422d-b447-1fa1a7ab1f5d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I have to pull out the chairs so that I can sit?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b949bea6-5b96-4569-9d42-5c9eee7fdb5a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I have to wipe the whiteboard before I start writing something?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "4d6319bf-574d-44d0-9822-6a0414ef5178",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the whiteboard eraser?",
    "answer": "on the whiteboard",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "2b318c1e-9c7e-4432-9961-94d0ee30b684",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the white board tray",
      "on the whiteboard",
      "on the whiteboard sill",
      "next to the table with four chairs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "on the wall",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "192218eb-ac51-49c9-8626-a36227a52f12",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/152-scannet-scene0494_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the white wall",
      "at the back of the room",
      "on the wall across the doorway",
      "on the white wall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black object besides the desk?",
    "answer": "chair",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "e9654e06-a447-4999-b7a0-e2fbb08c7ba6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the red object on the bed?",
    "answer": "mattress",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "fc104110-2148-4d9e-a8d8-d03c790a35fb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the garbage bin?",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "407a31fe-8dcf-4def-8b99-8118b84b0132",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the mattress?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "ac61cf15-2114-4e6f-b187-4c9094a60f70",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black object between the desk and the bed?",
    "answer": "chair",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "19fb8649-37e1-4215-9eeb-260da276db56",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the transparent object between the desk and the bed?",
    "answer": "window",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "3b60d924-e584-4328-9259-b38fb590b528",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the desk occupied?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "ca996036-7fde-4f2e-be26-e7d54bbe027f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I go out this room without opening the door?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "2652525c-79f2-4dba-a149-b898ca1c273c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is someone living here?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "0cf004a7-dab9-4bfe-8018-8e49cfda669d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I store some of my belongings under the bed?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "be70144d-654f-47ef-b060-554680db7c8a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the drawer (under the table) open?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "e1b47f95-7ae0-417f-8f3e-d096feae96f6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the brown two-level drawer?",
    "answer": "under the desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "a5c95b56-0ac2-472e-a06b-156e612df5e2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/154-scannet-scene0193_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "under the desk",
      "under the desk next to the chair",
      "under the brown desk, to the left",
      "under the brown desk right in front of the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the green object next to the coffee machine?",
    "answer": "lip balm",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "8cd1c57a-5449-4350-a263-f692dad8533f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many pots and pans are there on the stove?",
    "answer": "3",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "84833f1f-9c9b-4171-b948-88cfb0a3527a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape is the painting on the wall?",
    "answer": "rectangle",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "608fdb81-08e3-4fe3-9d32-11ff576721dd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the water bottle that is behind the paper towel?",
    "answer": "blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "68d072a5-274f-4348-bf10-ec2143dd2a80",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is in between of the black pot and the pan?",
    "answer": "grey pot",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "28fd88c3-a292-4b88-b443-156d6170eff6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there space for me to put something right next to the sink on the right hand side?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "e08b042f-b7c4-4578-b5af-3450566fc595",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the fridge open?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "6d24c042-126a-4068-a812-730c966dce04",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the pan empty?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "7722b8d2-c5aa-4419-8124-b0d9a0f83a0c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What objects could you possibly find inside the ref box next to the microwave?",
    "answer": "coke can",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "e76c10c6-79a0-464c-9a1b-2b67cf58a142",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there cleaning solutions for dirty plates?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "3d38c9f1-64a5-4e19-9715-5c4f4b7a818e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can be used as the quickest way to warm up my lunch?",
    "answer": "microwave",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "4051918b-c777-4ea8-b3e3-623e1ab88cbe",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I possibly find in the blue and white box next to the red box?",
    "answer": "beer",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "c929797a-967c-4159-83af-fa24bbe9c32e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is on the left of the grey pot?",
    "answer": "a pan",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "ea47a6d6-7eac-4f00-875b-5526a80c4c24",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "nonstick pan",
      "frying pan",
      "a pan ",
      "some beer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what is on the left of the black pot?",
    "answer": "a grey pot",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "dedb7582-1a78-4c3f-87d4-9a32d48dab5a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/155-scannet-scene0164_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "a gray pot",
      "gray pot with lid",
      "a grey pot",
      "the other stove burner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the grey object in the corner?",
    "answer": "armchair",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "756b2cd3-c58f-4299-899d-fa5da312d642",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black object in between armchairs?",
    "answer": "end table",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "2ad61ec5-3dd3-4eae-9158-af06871c07e2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "what shape is the end table?",
    "answer": "square",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "77414bbe-8e8c-4f99-bbf9-a2fb0476cb72",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "what color is the armchair?",
    "answer": "grey",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "d0c4c586-b8b8-4eee-8abc-9bccbaa03134",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can a person stand between two armchairs?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "538e2eb4-b91b-4531-b115-9f4fcff51564",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this room spacious enough for a 6-people party?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "75aeb6c5-08b4-48a4-a63c-c24348c9e9b5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the window open?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "15c521f1-4798-498b-aaf5-41bc67b92e89",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the armchairs occupied?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "eef418be-0d01-439c-a9e3-e282c5dd137a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "where can I sit to rest?",
    "answer": "armchair",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "338713a1-c9a4-4ebc-b387-61409670d51a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "where can I place my food for comfortably having lunch?",
    "answer": "on the end table in between the armchairs",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "ac489e30-5954-40f2-9c6d-625a04cb0103",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the room in a very good lightning condition? ",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b7e4763f-1d21-4565-9ff9-82af0bd250fa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I mop the floor of this room if it is dirty?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "fd5f875a-c63c-4042-af45-32aa5a5bc450",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "which armchair is closer to the end table that is at the center of the room?",
    "answer": "the armchair on the right",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "ec1538a5-f35a-4e2d-a454-88cd9d3746b1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "the one to the right",
      "the one to the right of the end table",
      "right armchair",
      "armchair on the right"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "which armchair is right under the window?",
    "answer": "the armchair on the right",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "1b675207-bc40-4620-bd9f-926c45741f55",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/156-scannet-scene0461_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "the one to the right",
      "the one to the right of the end table",
      "right armchair",
      "armchair on the right"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the red object on the chari?",
    "answer": "a backpack",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "53792cd2-9d0c-4350-a28b-aef96bd435d2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Among all the chairs, what is the unique color of the chair?",
    "answer": "green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "9fb8aca7-a295-4224-8631-b6466b212dae",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "what color is my backpack?",
    "answer": "red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "3318164c-fe79-4d22-a5f3-9c281eb257bc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can 10 people sit in this room?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "0f4e8e46-129b-44d1-8201-95721841ce8c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is the small and white object near the backpack?",
    "answer": "a piece of paper",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "730f80f8-c65b-4774-b249-aa91abf7f88a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the plastic water bottle open?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "33722505-458f-44c2-92b3-4d16ad4cb38d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to write something on using my pencil?",
    "answer": "the piece of paper",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "1a94ff3a-d917-47c0-b906-7f8d4c8f88f5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Were students here lately?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "e80d81d5-d174-4dc9-821a-ba95df69bb71",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my unfinished Starbucks drink? ",
    "answer": "on the table near the front whiteboard",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "e67ab82a-e427-4b29-8fc2-1f7f290d4d18",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the second table from the front",
      "In the center of the second table. ",
      "On the second table from the front",
      "On the table near the windows"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my marker?",
    "answer": "on the white board in the front",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "e008feb4-b533-439a-bae4-5407e7f79ae7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/157-scannet-scene0015_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In the whiteboard tray.",
      "Near the whiteboard",
      "Above the brown table",
      "On the holder by the front white board"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What objects are on the table?",
    "answer": "Garbage bins",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "cb31bc51-b9b2-451f-8ce7-05032d84d48c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object that is attached on the brown door?",
    "answer": "a mirror",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "30ac302e-4445-4982-8202-3adbdf8d9682",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the garbage bin that is the closest to the door?",
    "answer": "blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "49040c95-b666-4304-b342-30765c75aa74",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the garbage bin that is the closest to the window?",
    "answer": "green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "5f567df1-4fb3-43cb-9060-181074da17ca",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the only object you can see in the other room?",
    "answer": "a bed frame",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "543e3191-296e-4afd-9625-2fe2897cba1c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I place my laptop on the desk to study?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "cfc1c54b-cff3-4ce6-b5ec-d75405103682",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the white door fully closed?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "8354e8e6-0752-4ab1-9a1d-ce769c2ece01",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the brown door near the desk closed?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "e4b5ea66-9102-4879-8462-024d1628ffc7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I call 911?",
    "answer": "using the phone hanging on the wall",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "9b0de2f8-11de-4dae-aa28-c4da93f0433e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I see myself?",
    "answer": "using the mirror on the door",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "0175891c-e182-478d-be8b-de1a10ff8540",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you guess what color are the shoes I'm wearing today?",
    "answer": "grey",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "1ab2a08f-2a78-458b-ac66-6939c3bb1330",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I sleep comfortably on the bed in this room without putting anything on it?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "d7aaf35f-60fd-471f-8fee-40cd27e40baf",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "where is the phone?",
    "answer": "hanging on the wall",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "95d652cc-afe2-426a-81bd-1dcef1e6c90a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "above the white cabinet",
      "to the right of the door",
      "to the left when you enter the room",
      "above the light brown drawers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object under the phone at the corner?",
    "answer": "a three-level cabinets",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "5b2c40fd-cee0-4a13-a9f1-d1ccf9b46521",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/158-scannet-scene0356_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "A cabinet",
      "A white table or cabinet",
      "three tier drawer",
      "dresser "
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the wall to the right of the stove?",
    "answer": "an electrical outlet",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "fb8c685f-3628-4689-a001-c4451aaabf03",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What large kitchen appliance are there two of?",
    "answer": "refrigerator",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "e1bc960b-6160-400f-9bdb-4a42bc286cc8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the appliances in the kitchen",
    "answer": "white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "94be8967-bea0-4dbb-b093-c7d104858905",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many burners are on the stove?",
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "8f0f903e-dd01-4f8c-b7fd-2ed820109656",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the sink relative to the dishwasher?",
    "answer": "to the right",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "0122f114-e1ae-4e86-816e-a8f91dcfea43",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the stove relative to the sink?",
    "answer": "across",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "b3c27d3d-4d42-421c-b4da-568ff939155f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the dishwasher on?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "3b4bc6d8-e8e1-4665-89ca-24139e48e51e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are all of the cabinet drawers closed?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "e6bb724b-0597-425c-a302-e9aea5e0031b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you boil water, fry an egg, and separately saute vegetables, beans, and a protein at the same time in this kitchen?",
    "answer": "Yes, you can boil the water in the microwave and use the stove for the remaining items.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "cf78a884-0e67-472c-ad53-1b18384ed5de",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we store items in between the refrigerators?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "2188a1f3-d188-44b6-a166-0794ccfcf9b2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which refrigerator is designed for left-handed people?",
    "answer": "the refrigerator on the left",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b52bc051-f6a3-4161-aec5-77e5a5dda875",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the sink?",
    "answer": "to the right of the dishwasher",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "afd23587-fd83-4e7e-a2d9-98e72aa5f37a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "in the kitchen, across from the stove",
      "across from the stove",
      "the counter on the left side of the kitchen",
      "across the stove"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the microwave?",
    "answer": "above the stove",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "5bed8a12-8b95-4fb7-8eb8-698a161d0bd3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/160-scannet-scene0488_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "above the stove",
      "under the cabinets above the stove",
      "across the room from the sink",
      "on the right side of the kitchen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the right of the faucet?",
    "answer": "the soap",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "04886cce-d272-46e0-9235-68eac465549a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the left of the faucet?",
    "answer": "lotion",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "7f14c156-3844-4d48-aebb-3484bb0d8e43",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What colors are in the painting next to the mirror?",
    "answer": "blue, white, and green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "e3e3de6d-326c-4978-b008-3b9dbb50f6f7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the shower curtain?",
    "answer": "green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "7df01652-e97a-4c7c-ba71-a6f62b838f38",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is above the mirror?",
    "answer": "lights",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "ee9b89be-08e4-40f5-ac0c-7bb760bc1559",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is under the hand towel?",
    "answer": "a stool",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "27102e3e-44e1-49f2-ac13-265f2dff8644",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the bathroom window open?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "aa55382f-d80e-4491-b664-f3d954a43239",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the water running in the sink?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "e9d1e760-bf58-4883-af35-b4b64ac6ae76",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is written on the papers hanging on the walls?",
    "answer": "instructions",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "3ecbe224-e2a8-4712-ba42-bca265cfc12e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What two items should be moved before using the shower?",
    "answer": "the shower curtain and the bath mat",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "61f9e7fa-25ef-4672-89f7-be4dbf224391",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are there instructions on the walls?",
    "answer": "the bathroom might be used guests",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "82f406a7-f8c6-4f82-9556-efa7fa8c99dc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where might cotton swabs be store in this bathroom?",
    "answer": "In the medicine cabinet above the sink",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "de7ac44b-1c0a-4629-b3f1-a5ea88cf9e41",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the hand towel?",
    "answer": "to the right of the sink",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "147a8d52-51a2-49cb-a096-b35bb6182800",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the towel rack",
      "Hanging on the wall to the right of the sink",
      "On the pole below the power outlet",
      "Above the brown stool"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the stool?",
    "answer": "under the hand towel",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "930d68b1-9fd7-4a41-8998-381d70a40de6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/161-scannet-scene0583_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "to the right of the sink",
      "below the hand towel on the towel rack",
      "to the right of the sink",
      "next to the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is hanging on the char?",
    "answer": "A sweater",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "5141dd1c-5c1d-4e8c-8953-d3842dc55f66",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the cylindrical object in the corner of the room?",
    "answer": "A poster tube",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "941a8571-d84b-4607-bf2e-5a6db7ddfccd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the tape dispensers?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "41939df6-c376-4034-bfb3-0ef1735ddf89",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the floor between the desks?",
    "answer": "a power strip and cables",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "cf028c5f-9f99-49fd-9dbb-8d1b8fb0786a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is attached to the cork board near the door?",
    "answer": "a binder clip",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "e74c1a31-b36d-40bc-aaad-0a92c730e0c8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the blinds closed?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "59b36645-7990-4a8a-b153-08ec8703d09a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I get more light to work at the desk?",
    "answer": "turn on the table lamp",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "0b3fbdc0-7a98-41d7-82b5-b4ee42a352b4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people can sit on chairs in this room?",
    "answer": "5",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "fff41696-739e-43a5-af42-0d6cb9b90b17",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this room on the ground floor of the building?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b2499e86-cd59-4809-84e7-a3b34ea4cc57",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people are intended to use this space for work?",
    "answer": "2",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "aee9e1df-66b1-45a4-b1ab-e52248239e93",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "behind the brown bookshelf",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "a64782de-d282-4472-9b80-1b596d55276e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/162-scannet-scene0535_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "to the left of the blue and white chair",
      "across the room from the desks",
      "above the brown shelves",
      "net to the black and white lounge chair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the small appliance to the left of the sink?",
    "answer": "a water carbonator",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "aa45b0b9-a5a3-47c0-9a78-85b45b448291",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the dish soap?",
    "answer": "orange",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "6e2b0a40-3b3d-4102-865d-2fa25bb72c96",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the chapstick?",
    "answer": "green",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "22ab3135-8e19-453a-a5dc-1dcd6cc19901",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03"
  },
  {
    "question": " What is just to the right of the coffee machine?",
    "answer": "the salt",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "c0d60534-93ed-4794-844e-dff5dad32b67",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is behind to box of Coca Cola?",
    "answer": "a toaster",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "db2a420c-151b-4e64-959a-9a91a377aafe",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the box of coca cola full?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "952a5413-67b6-4c36-b4b5-ab8456335199",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are any of the burners on?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "aebfdd0c-7c76-4fe2-9591-3509ae1040fd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the small appliance to the left of the sink used for?",
    "answer": "to carbonate water",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a6cff3da-7709-4eac-8e0f-52bfbd75f8cf",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there anything in the kitchen to help with dry lips?",
    "answer": "yes, chapstick",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "802a646e-26c9-4d45-94f9-7b0b011526d4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the hand towel?",
    "answer": "hanging on the stove",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "c6186284-cb4a-492c-92a2-2cab89e34959",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03",
    "extra_answers": [
      "hanging on the stove counter",
      "on the railing attached to the gas stove",
      "hanging on the oven door handle",
      "below the stove"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the toaster?",
    "answer": "to the right of the microwave",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "1a8ee437-7b23-4457-9d70-649ac771c83c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/163-scannet-scene0164_03",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the table counter behind the coke bottles",
      "on the table counter next to the microwave",
      "to the right of the microwave",
      "behind the coke and beer boxes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on top of the toilet?",
    "answer": "a towel",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "78024203-22aa-4470-9825-01fc1c0c0ba0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What items are on the ledge of the bathtub?",
    "answer": " a bath mat and a small bottle",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "7bca44df-2f82-42b2-949e-7d454a6edc0d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the shower head?",
    "answer": "silver",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "a3f4ad21-0d01-47cc-b654-0ee043b94dc5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the curtain?",
    "answer": "gold",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "343fce64-b48f-43de-98db-412ac640770b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is hanging on the curtain rod?",
    "answer": "a curtain and towel",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "50367414-92a1-4509-a75e-2d0f32421e9e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is behind the curtain?",
    "answer": "a bath mat",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "e054db36-4034-4740-aea3-95988b44c5fd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the toilet lid closed?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "6dad0a90-2bab-4363-951b-dc12e9f0a667",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the towel on the toilet used?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "754b7814-3d22-4686-bb60-ee945d091f85",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I place a bottle of shampoo while I shower?",
    "answer": "in the tray in the corner of the shower area or on the ledge of the bathtub",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a41bc6c5-db91-469c-8d0c-02f11c02e159",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I place another towel to dry?",
    "answer": "You can hang it over the left side of the shower curtain",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "79224127-c9eb-49dd-9eaf-b3fe6e0eb757",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the shampoo in the bathroom intended for travel?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "3f8e8ca6-3827-4c40-a062-000c20ea9f97",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What should I use the angled bar in the shower area for?",
    "answer": "for balance",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "9b955b63-7f1a-41cd-9892-a2e42a601ede",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the bath mat?",
    "answer": "on the tub",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "1ff26710-75bf-4e00-8d3f-400ef3a3e4fe",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "to the left of the shower curtains",
      "to the right of the toilet",
      "On the tub",
      "On the tub, at the right of the toilet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the fresh towel?",
    "answer": "on the toilet",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "cbec1143-0256-47d0-afe7-e0bb0227eba6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/165-scannet-scene0406_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "below the painting",
      "to the left of the bath tub",
      "On top of the toilet and on the shelves at it's right ",
      "On top of the toilet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What device is on the chair?",
    "answer": "an iPad",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "085188fe-cd62-4470-91e9-11c1eece341d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is my luggage?",
    "answer": "black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "ad98ce8a-17d2-4afb-ab0e-deed7bea4b55",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the pants on the chair?",
    "answer": "gray",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "b2c8ec35-7d7b-4879-8199-d6a7edf3968c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is under the crumpled piece of paper?",
    "answer": "paper",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "869f43e5-e477-4746-a852-4054c530fb58",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the space on the chair to sit?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "3a85f448-1665-4631-9bde-0571d6042934",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": " Is the bed made?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "7af67917-5517-425a-92be-c490dcb13104",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to watch a TV show?",
    "answer": "the TV or the iPad",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "d3dbe292-7a21-459e-a470-a7f96beab6d3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to carry some snacks on a hike?",
    "answer": "the backpack",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "30d5d84c-4e8a-4570-bf62-767d7041a54c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is likely the maximum number of people that are allowed to sleep in this room?",
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "6b70bac8-1534-44be-9dc1-0cf6964bff07",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this a private residence?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "0cebd5cc-310b-427d-95e8-c15ee427a59a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my room key?",
    "answer": "on the desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "f8845772-d45a-48b0-84f9-659f34072c3c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In the envelope on the desk.",
      "Near the paper on the desk.",
      "on the desk",
      "near the papers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": " Where is the bottled water?",
    "answer": "above the mini-fridge",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "5b985952-b8a2-438b-bd56-c407b8634d8a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/166-scannet-scene0435_03",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On top of the fridge.",
      "By the window.",
      "on the minifridge",
      "next to the windows"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is hanging on the rod?",
    "answer": "a coat hanger",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "4dce5e88-17cb-43bc-9e50-024d55f55665",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/167-scannet-scene0307_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on top of the faucet?",
    "answer": "a towel",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "54429657-7b83-487c-8aa0-8d1af39a89b4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/167-scannet-scene0307_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What material is the coat hanger made from?",
    "answer": "wood",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "2136c0e0-7c04-4876-8f4d-e7ba1519a618",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/167-scannet-scene0307_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the dryer closed?",
    "answer": "no",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "0e34bf46-83f4-4e30-9721-600eeb457c25",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/167-scannet-scene0307_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the shelves full?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "e3b376ec-db5d-4c4c-ba74-e7f6d4b6209f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/167-scannet-scene0307_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I get outside from this room?",
    "answer": "you can exit through the door that is closed",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "8c8f2bd9-da71-4e90-9bd2-a9bf2fcef574",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/167-scannet-scene0307_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are three functions of this room?",
    "answer": "laundry, storage, and showering",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "e891f05d-120d-4322-b0e7-8928fce1dae9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/167-scannet-scene0307_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the plant?",
    "answer": "on the window sill",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "5a5bd136-7beb-4111-bd0c-201368b77f32",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/167-scannet-scene0307_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the windowsill",
      "By the window",
      "on the window sill above the sinks",
      "on the window sill above the washer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my key to this room?",
    "answer": "in the lock on the door",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "9114bbf3-0bd2-44c5-adb5-903ac6fa46ab",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/167-scannet-scene0307_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In the door",
      "In the lock",
      "the key is in the door keyhole",
      "in the keyhole"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in the center of the room?",
    "answer": "A table.",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b3be3cbc-d382-40bb-b33f-d1b22d97220b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objects against the walls of the room?",
    "answer": "Chairs.",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "9c6de794-334a-44a5-b92c-3103e631eeb3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many different colors are the chairs in the room?",
    "answer": "Four colors. Black, yellow, red and blue.",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "d669ce4b-f6d6-4f5f-9f67-74d12cb0ef68",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the pen on the table?",
    "answer": "Blue.",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "c7d66b13-573b-4ead-8c75-1ff840a7e35d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chairs around the table are mainly of which color?",
    "answer": "Red.",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "8c892a94-be3e-4349-a91d-d1ba39d86012",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there room on the table?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "3aadb123-b0e1-49c2-9646-cc98a491cbe7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the door open or closed?",
    "answer": "Open.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "02c778b1-5d43-426d-885f-63f607ec8aa6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the window open or closed?",
    "answer": "Closed.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "8d00062f-15c0-42f4-83e7-913c1dd27b18",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I wipe the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "There is an eraser under the whiteboard and a tissue on the table.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "0e2c244c-5fad-428b-9941-3eaec0d499d6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I charge my phone.",
    "answer": "There is a socket in the corner of the room.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "b749aeb9-231c-4b3b-8e23-a56832792184",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I sleep in this room?",
    "answer": "The room seems to be an office and doesn't have a bed.",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "ff931bad-a1a8-4da6-92b3-3712eb015689",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I watch a movie in the room?",
    "answer": "There seems to be a projector screen and cables on the table. You should be able to connect a computer to the screen to watch a movie.",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "8a8e627c-9bae-49e1-a296-c95cf471979a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the TV remote?",
    "answer": "On the table.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "35f5560e-3c25-4c27-ac25-4252b40ab6ab",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the white table",
      "on the white table, towards the door",
      "on the table in front of the door",
      "in front of the black chair on the table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the eraser?",
    "answer": "Under the whiteboard.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "c5553811-fe5c-485a-8f02-ae545fbdb69e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/168-scannet-scene0655_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "near the white board",
      "on the ledge at the whiteboard",
      "on the sill of the whiteboard",
      "next to the markers on the sill"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the backpack?",
    "answer": "Red.",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "7dac6f5e-cd4f-43f5-b119-7f3234976d12",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/169-scannet-scene0695_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the lamp?",
    "answer": "White.",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "7d1b51ad-98ab-4644-88c1-45c749fd3564",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/169-scannet-scene0695_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there room on my desk?",
    "answer": "No.",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "509d1fe4-3b62-43f5-bd80-b9c8032241ba",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/169-scannet-scene0695_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I put a couch in this room?",
    "answer": "There is not enough free space for a couch.",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "ef5d0018-218d-4085-bbeb-5c858c5b627e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/169-scannet-scene0695_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the window open or closed?",
    "answer": "Closed.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "7fe0d260-e410-4615-95c7-c51f812516b0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/169-scannet-scene0695_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is my laptop on?",
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "c42b6463-ec4d-4272-a98b-c58738cee15b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/169-scannet-scene0695_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I watch a movie?",
    "answer": "There is a laptop on the desk and a monitor behind it..",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "68e13346-13e8-4f1d-a3be-91d7c6898ee5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/169-scannet-scene0695_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the art above the bed.",
    "answer": "A cloth with a star shaped art on it.",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "0bdec62e-12aa-4f28-9a22-6606c38a6691",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/169-scannet-scene0695_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my backpack?",
    "answer": "Against the bed.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "aa4cb415-802f-47c9-ba0b-1850079c97aa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/169-scannet-scene0695_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the floor under near the bed.",
      "near the drawers under the bed",
      "on the floor close to the chair",
      "on the floor next to the bed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What object is on the center of the desk, leaning against the wall with the window?",
    "answer": "A picture frame",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "1a3df144-fd64-4b56-8ad3-a2d7965ec6d7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape is the pencil holder?",
    "answer": "Cylindrical",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "117211e7-7172-4445-9126-38d1d5f358b2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the cabinets on the brown desk?",
    "answer": "yellow",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "ac9011e4-0040-4f0d-9828-fde9e1c7c029",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the left of the blue paper on the desk with the monitor?",
    "answer": "Pens",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "1bb3eae5-36b9-4947-ae30-88de6f0ae85c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is hanging on the wall perpendicular to the windows?",
    "answer": "A blackboard",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "86b5b84c-c6ba-421b-814c-769fe53cb1c5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the windows open or closed?",
    "answer": "Closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "f58e2705-dc78-4a04-ba4b-f89ba7cbc15f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the blackboard clean?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "b7efc03d-5c92-4a1f-87a8-461d4d97ef4a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there space to hang up another poster?",
    "answer": "Yes, to the left of the monitor",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "da762ec1-2ca2-4ca0-bfb0-20a71fc22b24",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to make a digital copy of the stack of papers on the desk?",
    "answer": "Use the scanner built in to the printer",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "14470554-f8c6-40e8-a301-46329e7a62ea",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to get rid of the stack of papers on my desk. Where should I put it?",
    "answer": "Place it in the recycling bin to the right of the desk with the monitor",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "0b727ffa-414d-4495-8c75-8e2688c8204f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the poster hanging?",
    "answer": "On the wall to the right of the monitor.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "0bc5df39-0a41-41ea-aebc-bfa733cbae3f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "right of the monitor",
      "next to the printer",
      "On the wall next to the computer monitor.",
      "On the wall to the left of the printer."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which desk is the turquoise mug on?",
    "answer": "On the desk to the right next to the window.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "baaee8af-461a-43bc-897e-8549dd792c56",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/170-scannet-scene0378_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "the wooden desk",
      "the desk near the window",
      "The desk facing the windows.",
      "The wooden desk. "
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the left of the garbage bin?",
    "answer": "minifridge",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "16414b2b-fe03-4bfe-94b0-ca7714fa4773",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the chair?",
    "answer": "A pair of shorts",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "f50c591a-0bfd-4215-afeb-92d56e7f56e2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the towel?",
    "answer": "dark grey",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "91e5ff12-cf3d-41af-98aa-046d64790af1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is underneath the blue container?",
    "answer": "A see-through plastic container",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "8d960341-0b09-4505-b4c5-a78149f8344c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there any room to work on the desks?",
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "aefa9d7f-f8ab-4373-8ceb-db1066e62f52",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are both chairs pushed in?",
    "answer": "No.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "d83a933e-10fc-478e-8d73-8f7ae266c55f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the bed made?",
    "answer": "No.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "a810284c-2d13-4f9d-9814-eb1b10c6e204",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm hot, what can I do?",
    "answer": "Turn on the dark grey fan.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "e014a9be-7436-4253-99fa-6ff6dcda4444",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "My roommate is sleeping and turned off the room lights, but I need to work on my homework, what should I do?",
    "answer": "Use the desk lamp",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "df6cc3a9-195b-4a84-92dc-4d4f53c5b6ca",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the black backpack?",
    "answer": "On the floor, next to the bed",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "548dcc0c-8812-4b08-bba2-9075d176ec0b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the floor right next to the bed",
      "on the floor next to the bed and shoes",
      "on the floor next to the fan",
      "on the floor, at the foot of the bed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the black and red whey protein container?",
    "answer": "On top of the desk shelf",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "24081174-8f10-4c45-83b1-11f83c60f46c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/171-scannet-scene0222_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on top shelf of the desk cabinet",
      "on the top shelf of the brown desk",
      "on the shelves on the desk",
      "on the top shelf of the desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the rectangular object on the center of the ceiling?",
    "answer": "A projector",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "3c4537d1-dbd6-4517-8e22-1248f8cd92aa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is underneath the projector screen?",
    "answer": "Blue chairs",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "d0b5f592-5e6f-462a-a19e-45d116eb1d67",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the hanging lights?",
    "answer": "Yellow",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "0b9f9893-66ce-42ef-b3a3-8ab4089b5394",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the chairs in the front of the room?",
    "answer": "Black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "1a7b8523-e257-486c-951b-37c8c31c8b6c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is underneath the table in the front of the room?",
    "answer": "A power strip",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "e2d967de-7120-406a-be59-770e836ba07f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you spin around in the chairs in the front of the room?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "5bcac554-9bee-4b31-8087-9535226086db",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I share a video to those in the room?",
    "answer": "Use the projector",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "04634367-4326-414b-9476-0e028c28e5b7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I charge my computer?",
    "answer": "Plug it into the power strip on the floor.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "adbb8868-f4d1-4348-ba8d-023eb87e4eb0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I reduce the sunlight in the room?",
    "answer": "Use the pull cords next to the window to lower the blinds",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "3d1421e4-634c-4ce0-962e-746b3d6e0ec2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the chalkboard eraser?",
    "answer": "Underneath the blackboard",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "bcf81c6f-66ef-4302-9538-87b68c655729",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In the chalk tray.",
      "In the chalk tray close to the window.",
      "on the ledge infront of the blackboard",
      "below the backboard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Hanging on the wall on the opposite end of the room.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "f40aaf6f-44ed-4d9e-b99b-c5c4d6fc2309",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/172-scannet-scene0496_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the wall opposite the blackboard.",
      "Between the two windows on the far wall.",
      "hanging on the wall next the window",
      "hanging on the wall between two windows "
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the green boxes?",
    "answer": "Copy Paper",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "0a3aea98-1bfe-4071-8bb4-823b0c4bcdd7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the green object on the black desk?",
    "answer": "Paper cutter",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "1f92c3e6-07b9-48ec-948a-4719914b867c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the handles on the brown cabinets?",
    "answer": "Silver",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "a428bdc5-7bd3-475a-89cb-f6540b7b70a3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is above the brown chairs?",
    "answer": "A bulletin board",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "054eac37-42f1-4870-84c3-1fa48f2a4b05",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there room on the black counter to work on a computer?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "5353ec9d-b80a-4e92-a13e-dfb9f8cb67d7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the garbage can lids open or closed?",
    "answer": "Closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "f4642668-774b-4fdf-9881-d91129c0b491",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there any paper in the printer?",
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "537f08da-a8a4-4295-9e10-bb718c95a9d5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "The printer ran out of paper, where can I get more?",
    "answer": "Open one of the green boxes of paper",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "f2e2e5ba-f88d-4675-931d-eeb84d9d122b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to the trim the edges of a document that I printed out?",
    "answer": "Use the paper cutter on the black counter.",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "0479de12-7feb-4c56-bb87-33849036a032",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the red and black poster?",
    "answer": "On the bulletin board",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "28f6a1cb-2ad9-43cd-874a-d62faed8a39b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the bulletin board next to the printer",
      "on the bulletin board",
      "On the Cork board",
      "On the cork board near the printing machine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the broom?",
    "answer": "Against the green wall.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "6d71161a-d796-4cf9-a83f-f598e53898de",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/173-scannet-scene0278_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "leaning against the walls next to the printer",
      "in the corner leaning against the bulletin board",
      "On the corner of the room, where the green wall and the Cork board match",
      "On the corner of the room, near the printing machine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black object above the sink?",
    "answer": "A soap dispenser",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "36d39635-96fa-4193-b7c1-8ef56a910dea",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the wall?",
    "answer": "Yellow",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "d3e612ec-fe15-41f9-b08e-d3bbcd43845a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the toilet paper holders filled?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "e2e83cc4-1f41-4de2-80d5-7e8a0a0a74d7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is below the sink?",
    "answer": "A floor drain.",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "2a9641dc-5950-4f24-83f2-5e38b543cba1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the silver object on the wall next to the second toilet?",
    "answer": "Garbage",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "0f3d6204-48d9-4205-9a03-d6a13109feb3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the sink running?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "1b0d4d46-70c0-4ac0-b75b-cdc7528df0b7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What might help a person in a wheel chair stabilize themselves while transitioning to the toilet?",
    "answer": "The grab bars above the toilet in the second stall",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "9b816c56-6cb0-4c45-9bc5-266c3a72e884",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do the toilets flush automatically or need to be flushed manually?",
    "answer": "Manually",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "19aa71b9-e542-4c87-9a52-bc8469c73f6e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of person is the larger bathroom designed for?",
    "answer": "Handicapped person",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "8a59074b-714e-470d-93d3-deddd354d1a6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Above the paper towel holder.",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "4bee5ae4-2d90-4de2-b009-8dfac4214368",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/174-scannet-scene0086_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "above the paper dispenser ",
      "above the paper dispenser and close to the trash can",
      "on top of the paper towel dispenser",
      "on the black box to the right of the two sinks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black object on top of the white cubby shelf?",
    "answer": "A hat",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "f38db842-3d5b-409f-9046-c4ac556a527c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/175-scannet-scene0329_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What colors are the cubby shelves in the office?",
    "answer": "Black and white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "2a357e6a-8917-4c46-9abe-1e6ae70e01a6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/175-scannet-scene0329_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is behind the clear and blue water bottle?",
    "answer": "A red metal water bottle",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "142551d7-1c44-47cb-9406-98a9a26b4e5c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/175-scannet-scene0329_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the black backpack?",
    "answer": "On the left of the brown couch",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "99e98610-d1b5-4b76-a47d-443523a64a16",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/175-scannet-scene0329_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the black garbage bin full or empty?",
    "answer": "empty",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "c55ca66e-c7e9-4163-85f1-2d90ea7f6917",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/175-scannet-scene0329_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the lamp next to the couch plugged in?",
    "answer": "No.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "f57420a6-fcf6-4cea-9cea-1e9083ee8570",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/175-scannet-scene0329_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to write a message for everyone in the office, what should I do?",
    "answer": "Write on the white board",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "296cbc1f-8f63-46de-a603-ff169a29e1ff",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/175-scannet-scene0329_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "If there's a loud, piercing, repetitive sound in the room, where is it coming from? ",
    "answer": "The fire alarm above the brown couch",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b6d30cdf-dc28-47f2-a169-0e5d95bb49e2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/175-scannet-scene0329_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the yellow eraser?",
    "answer": "On the whiteboard eraser",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "33f1e9ca-72e7-4c98-9b52-f6ddd4786483",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/175-scannet-scene0329_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the whiteboard.",
      "On the whiteboard to the right of the pictures.",
      "on the whiteboard",
      "to the right of the printed images"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is above the desk with the two monitors?",
    "answer": "A handdrawn painting",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "f0cbcb80-5363-429d-ac17-a873fc3d1e6d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/176-scannet-scene0643_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the mug next to the first monitor?",
    "answer": "The letter \"S\"",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "a92b5721-564f-480f-a44a-8f3cc46971a0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/176-scannet-scene0643_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the paper with the checkerboard on it?",
    "answer": "On top of the cooling unit",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "8a575099-723a-44a8-a8dd-43ef249b695e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/176-scannet-scene0643_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the stapler?",
    "answer": "To the right of the monitor",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "abc4646a-9ce6-4b97-ab29-95b8f96d65e6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/176-scannet-scene0643_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is today's date on the calendar?",
    "answer": "June 6",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "55e2853b-90d0-4bd2-9177-8012dc527f82",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/176-scannet-scene0643_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is missing on the second desk?",
    "answer": "A keyboard and mouse",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "1ad1eb7e-bd2a-4b29-b8f5-cca18a9c2c0c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/176-scannet-scene0643_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the monitor on the second desk next to the blue object old or new?",
    "answer": "Old, it uses VGA",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "4eb752c4-4144-426c-84f8-58ef6f312858",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/176-scannet-scene0643_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the lime bottle?",
    "answer": "Next to the desk, in front of the telephone",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "662747e8-e569-4194-87cb-7e247f75b683",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/176-scannet-scene0643_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "next to the phone",
      "on the mini-fridge",
      "On the white desk.",
      "In front of the telephone, on the desk. "
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the brown bag?",
    "answer": "In the grey trash can",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "a46aaed6-b8c5-4584-8902-c6aff7ecfde4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/176-scannet-scene0643_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "in the trash",
      "in the gray trash can",
      "In the trash can.",
      "In the grey bin."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the right of the guitar?",
    "answer": "A massage chair",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "95cfe5bb-f8f7-4852-b3b9-e0ab26e69189",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is hanging from the curtain pole?",
    "answer": "A soccer banner",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b15ba31e-4f17-4a44-b39b-7ce8fdc51e3f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What colors are on the soccer banner?",
    "answer": "Blue, green, and white",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "12413747-197f-4fde-870e-f75a411b1d96",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What material is the massage chair?",
    "answer": "Leather",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "62a476a5-b00b-4942-a5b7-ad0b5fae0868",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the right of the plant and to the left of the piano?",
    "answer": "The guitar",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "59e2c378-e4ea-4d1b-a4ad-94ee573c6722",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is to the left of the painting?",
    "answer": "A world map",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "20ceb9d6-4817-4953-9acb-51d2a40668af",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a light on inside the room?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "f9ac7781-f427-4c21-879e-d41894e7c0a1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the chess board set up?",
    "answer": "No.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "50cf39e2-38cf-4dbc-9e34-d33877d1a2b3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I play and sing a song from the couch?",
    "answer": "Use the guitar",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "89a32dbf-a2ca-424c-9396-84459bc8f67b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to help me sleep on the couch?",
    "answer": "The neck pillow",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "82e1e544-2d9f-4755-9815-568dee56ff66",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What team is the owner of this room a fan of?",
    "answer": "Chelsea International",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "9b0e9f41-203c-4969-b713-17f4bc5152a9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What might be the profession of the owner of this room?",
    "answer": "A musician",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "29833f6e-eb10-4c6d-87e2-4824f837fce7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Above the microwave",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "bd921f39-d628-4fee-8026-7e3231008e07",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "above the microwave",
      "above the microwave close to the plant",
      "on the wall above the microwave",
      "on the wall in the adjacent room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the neck pillow?",
    "answer": "On top of the piano keyboard",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "b161deae-a42d-4fcb-b3b8-173016cf90d9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/177-scannet-scene0608_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the piano keyboard",
      "on the piano keyboard below the sport team posters",
      "on the keyboard, in front of the window",
      "on the keyboard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is behind the garbage bin?",
    "answer": "A circuit breaker box",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "6caf59bf-2792-44e6-8784-c65697c476e8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the large object at the end of the room?",
    "answer": "A poster printer",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "baee041f-b8a3-4cb4-889c-ea7575692ed3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color are the latches on the circuit breaker box?",
    "answer": "Red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "a08d95f2-94e9-4b7a-9797-9e06f9d99920",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the paper trimmer board long or short?",
    "answer": "Long",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "63fc5ed4-5074-4657-baa1-070c98bd698a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is directly on top of the black desk?",
    "answer": "A paper trimmer",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "a5ea1265-f3e8-4ab8-a7d1-82d1198e8067",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the black wire?",
    "answer": "Underneath the poster printer",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "37c9a32b-ec45-4bba-aec5-d0abafd4b0d8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the tape running out?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "87df940b-ce37-475f-80d9-ed650007b065",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there things inside the garbage bin?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "dba4a507-03d9-47a1-aebf-78eba47dd2c3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of items can go in the green bin?",
    "answer": "Paper",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "ec2171d3-6232-4a28-907e-f2baa0dde9e9",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the light goes out, what should I do?",
    "answer": "Check the circuit breaker box",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "c5f1c860-5c73-4566-bfcb-f5652b3160c6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "The poster I printed has a lot of white margin, how can I fix this?",
    "answer": "Use the paper trimmer",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "329be55d-4f68-42ef-839d-e2d11cfe2fe1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this a person's home?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "ad3fbe74-ade5-4cf3-9f6c-c3a3b99f3a9c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did I leave the tape?",
    "answer": "On the right edge of the brown desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "fb924bca-7575-46a9-8f5c-b4b0e6caa4ab",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the corner of the brown desk.",
      "On the desk by the stack of papers.",
      "on smaller brown table",
      "on the small table infront of the printing machine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the painting?",
    "answer": "To the right of the green garbage can",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "ea0ad67c-1f8f-4779-8928-5f11c6980dc1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/178-scannet-scene0685_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Leaning against the wall behind the door. ",
      "Leaning agains the circuit breakers.",
      "right of the garbage bin",
      "on the floor in the corner next to the garbage bin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on top of the brown desk?",
    "answer": "A blue backpack",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "be856696-0ed5-44a4-8dee-ecb5b59438fd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on the red wall next to the monitors?",
    "answer": "The light switch",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "c3abc41f-789c-43be-a1c2-b60cf362bcf3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the walls behind the book shelf?",
    "answer": "Burgandy",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "4132f403-879b-457b-961c-f95df12748a0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the material of the chairs?",
    "answer": "Grey fabric",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "226a9672-6811-4268-82b9-e2daddedf289",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the chairs tucked into the table?",
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "bf533bc8-570f-446c-ae76-a339a0dd87c1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the window shades opened or closed?",
    "answer": "Closed.",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "35e45750-271d-4206-a9bf-b962edae3860",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the bookshelves mostly full or empty?",
    "answer": "Full",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "e905cd18-c01f-423a-a853-2b52b10ff6ff",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where should I put the wire to charge my computer if I'm sitting at the desk with the backpack on it?",
    "answer": "Pass the wire through the silver latch",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "7bdd4863-03d3-44c4-bbd8-f11d31d40d87",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to find where a particular book is located?",
    "answer": "Use the catalog on the computer",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "e1f9b6b4-cf8f-417f-aa85-e32d6db75a77",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this room on the ground floor?",
    "answer": "No.",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "3e91cd44-957c-4ff1-87f0-b93420aa93f7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the state of the room, should the lights be turned off or kept on?",
    "answer": "Turned off",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "16314d65-bc36-438b-8561-4720a7084beb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is my blue waterbottle?",
    "answer": "Inside the backpack on top of the wooden desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "2c6e4c06-e365-4b80-ab32-e7faee03f9af",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/179-scannet-scene0300_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In the pocket of the backpack.",
      "In the backpack on the desk.",
      "next to the blue backpack",
      "at one of the workstations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object in the floor near the door that exits the restroom?",
    "answer": "A pair of slippers",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "a47013cb-309f-4494-9b32-bbc38edcc23b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the pink object in the corner?",
    "answer": "A cloth",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "defc68ed-4671-4678-969f-75ae0243c577",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which material are the drawers from the vanity made from?",
    "answer": "Wood",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "670fd19f-1fe6-4232-a486-e69be7393bd3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which shape is the restroom sink?",
    "answer": "Oval",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "8673ad9c-1447-4fd6-8aa8-6bd64748568b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the tall object between the restroom sink and the wall?",
    "answer": "An electric toothbrush",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "48de5c9f-014d-400c-8cbc-e714fee34744",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you locate yourself watching at the restroom sink and do a 180 degree turn, what would you see?",
    "answer": "The restroom door",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "f01f4122-72ce-45d5-a3f7-869d8c24bd6f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the toilet open or closed?",
    "answer": "Closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "2cc52fa0-f32b-491f-89eb-85fae00f7eed",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there water running from the faucet of the restroom sink?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "d25e0e56-6873-46d6-9a62-c7bcfc405e24",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I dispose of small bathroom waste items like tissue paper?",
    "answer": "In the trash bin",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "bb936e73-356d-4b21-8924-a0329aac1b9c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I wear from the scene to warm my feet?",
    "answer": "The pair of slippers",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "a5b5d845-3a6f-4251-83e9-ba5830fede4a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I take a bath or only a shower?",
    "answer": "A bath",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "254e8ed6-a9da-4595-aa86-b6f53e253dfa",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to watch myself?",
    "answer": "The mirror",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "aef5ef60-1ae5-40ab-be92-d9633b6aad66",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the blue bath robe hanging from?",
    "answer": "From the door",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "4db64c99-2808-46c2-b71e-bacbd5273ec8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "From the white door",
      "The hook on the door",
      "back of the bathroom door",
      "a hook on the door"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the electric toothbrush?",
    "answer": "On top of the bathroom vanity",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "75797944-2d04-43ae-863e-4568b71c517c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/180-scannet-scene0100_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "to the right of the sink",
      "to the right side of the bathroom counter",
      "right of the sink",
      "on the right of the bathroom counter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is over the table?",
    "answer": "A computer",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "e09cba21-13bb-4856-8fc1-386de7c0a83a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/181-scannet-scene0314_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What material are the chairs made of?",
    "answer": "Leather",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "0d62ea77-d02b-4ec2-b7eb-4f84ca421da2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/181-scannet-scene0314_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which color are the chairs?",
    "answer": "Black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "cf153ba8-dd50-4ad4-8c3a-c1e322bacfb8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/181-scannet-scene0314_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is at the center of the table?",
    "answer": "A lamp",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "50f4f7db-d50c-42f4-92fe-82387db91e0a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/181-scannet-scene0314_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the lamp on or off?",
    "answer": "On",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "bfb9dbe4-c22e-4408-bd60-45d09a239484",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/181-scannet-scene0314_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What can I use to better light my workspace in this room?",
    "answer": "The lamp at the center of the table",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "c38b2190-e647-47e8-aa8f-5ea617198e30",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/181-scannet-scene0314_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I set up a place to study?",
    "answer": "In the table with the computers.",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "47ee33f1-a56d-4ea5-a746-75861ef25ad6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/181-scannet-scene0314_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are the computers?",
    "answer": "Over the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "29777777-f691-4781-93e1-afc066900b2a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/181-scannet-scene0314_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the round wooden desk",
      "on the circular desk",
      "Around the light fixture",
      "On top of the table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is on top of the nightstand besides the lamp?",
    "answer": "A clock",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "2a90b1f9-1f60-436a-807f-b436881e3592",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the small and long black object on top of the right bed?",
    "answer": "Tv remote control",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "85c329e0-a144-41e6-a2c0-11ec3e261bab",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which color is the linen of the bed?",
    "answer": "White",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "86eac1db-ef9b-4f9f-bfbc-6acdb5f32ed6",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What material is the floor of the room made of?",
    "answer": "carpet",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "cff4127b-c5cb-4c4a-b3b5-52373e573f65",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between the two beds?",
    "answer": "A nightstand",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "f52da6f8-061c-4cdb-a99d-6b3b91469838",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the light on or off?",
    "answer": "The light is on",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "80bf5f9e-1c45-432e-9d29-1f1c8f3b716e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the nightstand clean of full of things?",
    "answer": "Clean",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "0ca99f77-6c99-4696-9352-eb651de75ce0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there anything on this scene that I can use to tell the time? If so what?",
    "answer": "Yes, the clock in the nightstand",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "1f1bed27-29f7-40eb-861d-40258be57f2f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there something I can use to manipulate the TV? If so what?",
    "answer": "Yes, The remote on top of the bed",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "35639cf3-9253-4f17-8cfb-bca56a1ed1f8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the remote?",
    "answer": "Over the bed",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "0c2896fc-c4a2-42be-b9cb-b0274cc94cf0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the bed that's closer to the window",
      "near the laptop on the bed",
      "To the left of the notebook",
      "On the edge of the bed on the right"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can you find a painting?",
    "answer": "Hanging on a wall over the bed",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "440b8568-0390-4e9e-9955-74fb535f3616",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/182-scannet-scene0645_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "above each bed",
      "above the head of the bed",
      "On the wall above the bedframe",
      "Above the heardboard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the small object on the center of the table",
    "answer": "A pen",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "846bca34-e9a3-4e6a-9edd-8358da559a64",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the chair on front of the desk?",
    "answer": "Black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "2f26e7c5-b4f4-4d78-b2ac-7cda9f325b37",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape is the carpet on the floor?",
    "answer": "Rectangular",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "8367e3f6-9f99-4119-818c-615ada957972",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object on the floor between the desk, the couch and the trash can? ",
    "answer": "A lamp",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "8c04ba45-b59c-4cc1-b945-10bee659ba4f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were to sit on the black chair in front of the desk and see the wall, you'll see some objects hanging, which are those?",
    "answer": "Medals",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "01743cec-192c-48c0-8017-fa0c33ea7616",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the desk clean or full of things?",
    "answer": "Full of things",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "f86e8cc7-d1b1-432f-b8e0-de5760e575c5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the trash can empty?",
    "answer": "No, it's full",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "6999b759-8c14-42de-b448-1d6154eb8917",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I work in this place?",
    "answer": "In the desk",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "3a73d258-b531-4504-9712-d6344e6d3d9f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there somewhere here where I can take a nap? If so where?",
    "answer": "Yes, the couch",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "256c9e92-2dea-4152-8c84-4dfd881a3b96",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the paper bag?",
    "answer": "On the floor",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "d07e539d-22b5-43e2-9d13-d8394daf3706",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/183-scannet-scene0231_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "next to the couch",
      "on the floor",
      "on the carpet next to the couch",
      "on the carpet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the black object bellow the desk?",
    "answer": "A trash can",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "6a34cb99-a449-4071-aba6-357d1c7a943d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which color is the chair?",
    "answer": "Black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "fdf4e7e5-c31b-4546-a884-c9619d4e8ff2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which are the two principal colors of the painting?",
    "answer": "White and Black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "8ffd24c9-1b04-4a14-97be-f1448354f3bc",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object that is currently placed on the upper part of the desk, near the wall, on the left side?",
    "answer": "A coffee machine",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "0cf2b29c-af4c-4a50-9646-5aba1b3034ec",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the object on the floor between the desk with the chair and the black cabinet?",
    "answer": "A suitcase",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "b9082f55-b06a-4680-a6a9-3f454d261a52",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the light on the desk on or off?",
    "answer": "On",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "64631b89-cdd4-42d4-a3dc-53d052ddc8df",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the suitcase on the floor open or closed?",
    "answer": "Closed",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "17215d78-a356-4ade-b84a-fabb161f9c38",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there an object in this scene to prepare a coffee? If so where is it?",
    "answer": "Yes, the coffee machine on the desk",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "c653292e-cfce-4d69-bb3e-7994d220de47",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I sit to work?",
    "answer": "On the chair in front of the desk",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "7e0d4b86-9102-4afa-abdc-c8a8f59823d2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Im thirsty, is there something I can drink? If so what is it?",
    "answer": "Yes, water",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "9f378b85-bd57-4776-93b2-8148e6c5784d",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the room on this scene?",
    "answer": "A hotel room",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "b85a44e7-0383-45aa-ae10-ecb951c1d5a8",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the suitcase?",
    "answer": "On the floor",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "ec077b83-1848-4194-9203-b33e11802f73",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "In front of the door.",
      "To the right of the desk.",
      "on the floor, right in front of the door",
      "on the floor next to the desk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the trash can?",
    "answer": "On the floor, bellow the desk",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "e204ce82-2602-4c28-bcf8-c8cfb2bf693f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/185-scannet-scene0435_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Under the desk.",
      "To the left of the chair under the desk.",
      "under the desk",
      "next to the desk chair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the tall object on the corner?",
    "answer": "A plant",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "5c9e876f-a4dd-4ce9-8e96-245ab1b2df94",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object over the side table?",
    "answer": "A jar with flowers",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "ac7b12cc-0c32-4de3-8059-7bdf0f2793bd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which material are the side and center tables?",
    "answer": "Wood",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "007b3e02-d944-4c04-9bce-f037adcf34bf",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which color are the sofas?",
    "answer": "Blue",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "917d4feb-7e7a-4f9f-a1b0-17451a9fd5bb",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were to sit on the long blue couch, which object will you see on your left over the table?",
    "answer": "A jar with flowers",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "846b9dc5-2309-46b0-ae83-f89c1a8511a7",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is between the two blue armchairs?",
    "answer": "A table",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "aee1ab06-4fc0-4238-a50b-bb8ed35ac956",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a long table between the three couches, is it clean or cluttered?",
    "answer": "Clean",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "2d8aa869-37eb-4d16-9b2c-ceb0fd8fc00a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I rest?",
    "answer": "On the couch or the armchairs",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "598c23b2-c8a1-4b90-ba63-7bcb2a113e03",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you see a place to charge my phone? If so where?",
    "answer": "Yes, there are some wall outlets near the couch",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "acf5dc41-c6a9-42f3-b76b-14d120aa19e1",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there something that lives in this scene? If so what?",
    "answer": "Yes, there's a plant and some flowers",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "35ccfa71-67e1-42c7-bd8c-e375348beab0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the jar with flowers?",
    "answer": "Over the side table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "cb07597c-0331-4434-9f5a-c93d5c9f6629",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/186-scannet-scene0549_01",
    "extra_answers": [
      "On the side table near the blue couch.",
      "On the circular wooden table. ",
      "On the table between the blue sofas",
      "Above the small table with 4 legs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the red objects on the room?",
    "answer": "Chairs",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "5da047fb-bf0b-4ad6-bc8b-a715f05bdd78",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "There's something coming out of the table, what is that?",
    "answer": "Cables",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "cfc605af-6ea0-4b95-92c2-df0812f38722",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which color are most of the chairs?",
    "answer": "Red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "483e26cc-ba2d-465f-a1ca-8838277627b5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which color are the borders of the table?",
    "answer": "Red",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "81e68663-224f-4f56-b598-e29f093d9b05",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were to sit on the yellow chair you would see a chair in front of you, which color is it?",
    "answer": "Red",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "5e83797c-0eef-4dae-8f8c-84050d581c33",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Walk to the center whiteboard facing to it. Now do a 180 degree turn, which furniture do you see directly in front of you?",
    "answer": "Table and Chairs",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "7e4d6420-013b-422d-a47f-7a1a8015e0f2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the whiteboard clean or it has something written?",
    "answer": "It has something written",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "2cc802ce-d0ec-44ff-8b60-de056083f56c",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there space in the table for me to put my computer?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "a8f5e240-7d09-4d5f-84e9-65549d1c54ed",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can I write something?",
    "answer": "On the whiteboard",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "f060bdfd-266d-448a-adf1-133ec140ca52",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I project my computer using the cables from the scene?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "4701e80a-f33b-4d59-851e-7fa52bffa55a",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there something over the table that I can use to write on the whiteboard? If so what?",
    "answer": "Yes, the marker",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "e7f5a4e1-eeb3-4bd8-96ad-8eb421d75f72",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which room is this?",
    "answer": "A conference room",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "7fc60162-4f96-4d1a-9130-3f2d66c24f0b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the blue marker?",
    "answer": "On the table",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "a8c2bb22-48e8-4d9d-a3f7-d3e82740cffe",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the table",
      "on the table with the wires",
      "Standing upright on the table.",
      "On the corner of the table near the whiteboard."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the eraser?",
    "answer": "On the whiteboard",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "334154b8-edea-4fdf-964f-2d29cd553f08",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/187-scannet-scene0655_02",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the whiteboard",
      "on the whiteboard tray",
      "In the marker tray.",
      "In the center of the marker tray by the whiteboard."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the white machine over the green countertop?",
    "answer": "A printer",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "b16560d5-f3cd-4646-a21b-7cce061a31b3",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "There's a big machine on the floor, what is it?",
    "answer": "A printer",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "f748d6a3-286f-4fc0-9a9e-1649a83e662e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which material is the chest of drawers?",
    "answer": "Wood",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "16b19f88-4317-4e03-8817-e39f7320406b",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are two trash cans, which color are them?",
    "answer": "Black",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "31354b71-c5e7-4c9a-b938-fd18c7515bd4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are two trash cans, notice the smallest one. Does it has a plastic bag in it or not?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "49189243-1a64-4ac6-a32a-6aaf80ec6837",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Position yourself such that the big trash can is on your left and the green furniture is in front of you, which object is on your right?",
    "answer": "A fan",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "fb01a002-672b-4000-925d-78e3dac8ef29",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the big printer on of off?",
    "answer": "On",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "1f420b3a-42af-4c49-a6f1-51982b95c481",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there something to cut paper? If so where is it?",
    "answer": "Yes, over the chest of drawers",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "d3792585-2b71-41c7-9148-c6bd6b2d4754",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there something to wipe my nose? If so where is it?",
    "answer": "Yes, over the chest of drawers",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "98d630c9-6689-4a26-892f-4290c150f984",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the room predominately used for?",
    "answer": "To make copies",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "39da40fe-2b93-4961-b878-acb32fd0df6f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm getting hot, what can I do?",
    "answer": "Turn on the fan",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "e8fb6560-0d0a-4ede-aabc-76cec239f14e",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the Kleenex box?",
    "answer": "Over the chest of drawers",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "e157bc4e-ac21-4327-af28-4ac18d161778",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the brown drawers next to the window",
      "on the drawer chest next to the window",
      "on the wooden cabinet near the window",
      "to the left of the paper cutter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a paper cutter? If so where?",
    "answer": "Yes, over the chest of drawers",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "8e0a0270-9031-48ec-8372-9c0d49d02a84",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/188-scannet-scene0593_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "on the brown drawers next to the window",
      "on the drawer chest next to the window",
      "yes, on the wooden cabinet in front of the window",
      "right next to the big recycle bin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the most predominant furniture in the scene?",
    "answer": "Chairs",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "9e4381a0-7745-48a2-a123-669524352dd4",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the blue object in the ground?",
    "answer": "A trash can",
    "category": "object recognition",
    "question_id": "9e900d39-f553-4ffe-937a-f81944c78634",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which material is the furniture of the scene?",
    "answer": "Wood",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "00371545-9660-4dfd-94a8-4cae5f07bc14",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are two boards side by side, which color are they?",
    "answer": "White",
    "category": "attribute recognition",
    "question_id": "2854b5f9-4494-47dd-a394-67f3f8c81905",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were to position yourself looking at the whiteboard and then do a 90 degree turn to the right, what will you see in the wall? ",
    "answer": "A window",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "c5fbce6d-e4bc-43cf-984a-4efc2fde01e0",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Theres a red and black marker over a shelf, what is bellow them on the ground?",
    "answer": "A trash can",
    "category": "spatial understanding",
    "question_id": "c527196b-f103-4e34-8899-ec8e5afa6bf5",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the whiteboards clean or they have something written in them?",
    "answer": "They have something written",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "bddda2b0-4f5b-4b4d-9306-ec560ebf1b9f",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the blue trash can empty or full?",
    "answer": "Full",
    "category": "object state recognition",
    "question_id": "12d8846e-83e7-4b0a-8aec-2611b5bce574",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there something that can tell the time in this scene or not?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "2e2b709a-e16c-4cb9-b8c3-8a4e68aa8283",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there something to watch a movie on this scene or not?",
    "answer": "No",
    "category": "functional reasoning",
    "question_id": "43f61659-5531-47c6-b766-98dcc472e526",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main purpose of this room?",
    "answer": "To teach",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "60cb4642-5d6d-4a72-b743-ceeb82531cb2",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "There's something written on the whiteboard, what does it look to you?",
    "answer": "Math Equations",
    "category": "world knowledge",
    "question_id": "83bdc83b-e5ad-42fd-a0ba-2a1fdf2002ef",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the blue trash can?",
    "answer": "On the floor",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "f1265e16-4dad-4c8d-95d0-c0029893b9bd",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "to the right of the gray trashcan",
      "To the left of the white board",
      "near the whiteboards",
      "under the built in workstation on the left"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Hanging on the wall",
    "category": "object localization",
    "question_id": "6ef3413f-bde6-40ec-bd4a-48f620de4445",
    "episode_history": "scannet-v0/189-scannet-scene0500_00",
    "extra_answers": [
      "Above the chairs on the wall",
      "To the right of the window",
      "back of the classroom",
      "between the two windows at the far end"
    ]
  }
]